On to tarot stack and angels whisper through ice sheets, I can feel the static moon hanging from the telephone
Battles move, I show the signal, survive, transmission keepin' dead hearts alive
And every lone otter here in this tomb only says she's totally human
While Eden crackers behind the shed, but her little raccoon fingers
Keep revealing her instead She wears sunglasses after midnight
And growls at every foo- Shiny objects and absolutely never explains why
Is a glamour leopard, Patricia Oh, she drinks, cives her gold plates
Patricia says, darling, you're fair, Joni Shrieks, you've been
Just to unplug Joni's jukebox scene.
Rattrisha Pookser whiffs using my butt flip.
Rattrisha, come on.
Sock it.
Well, I do have one more.
The male psyche, but also the female psyche.
But I'm the male psyche.
But there is a female psyche, too.
Like, actually, the real psyche is actually a female psyche.
The goddess psyche.
So it's a special little tribute.
Pressure creates diamonds.
I'm good. I'm good. I'm on an odd sleep schedule once more, but it's okay. I am very relaxed. I am rested
Got some creative stuff done got some other stuff done. What would you like a piece of
Original media I just created
All right, let me put it backstage. How are you doing? I'm great. I got a lot of work done today too and
Yeah, the codex I haven't logged in yet, but I'm excited because I want to do the review
I know I've been saying I'm gonna do it, but I want to make sure everything's working. Yeah
I'm glad because uh, yeah, it's been one thing after another, but I am getting pretty good at like learning
like a lot of stuff like I've learned so much since I started like
you've basically gone through a course and
Just from doing it
It's been months. Yeah. And it's like, you know, learning how like, I mean, even it's still like,
you know, going to Google and like trying to figure out like, what's going, I have like $1,300
of credits they gave me. I need to figure out how to use those, you know, it's like, I must use,
but it's like, yeah, I can use it all on like their and also like a lot of programs or a lot of
You've got to get into that. That's so you. That's for you.
It's so cool because it's like everything is way cheaper. Everything is discounted.
They really want people to be developers and I guess like 1% of people...
Know how to code, you know, and now it's kind of like now that there's more people by coding and stuff
It's like there's people that have never designed or done programming
Building things now and that's pretty amazing. I mean, yeah
I'm just you said to tell it what to make and it will make it and you have to do like yeah
Yeah
it's crazy all right well i put well before you play what i put backstage but before you play it
have you been keeping up with the uh cue and crystal saga
I just saw like she put a thumbnail of like them having like Chinese food or something like that or like their dinner or something like
It's getting it's getting intense more so than you think
Apparently see I missed I had to catch up on the syndication site today because that there was no way
but um
Apparently, she allegedly went on a date and she wanted Q2B jealous.
Did she really go on a date?
I don't know.
Grateful 2026 or INX.
She thinks it's a lie.
I listened to the exchange that was supposedly her getting ready to go on the date and I
that that anvil you know um I he inspires me it's so evil for real I mean
the things that he the way he is puppet master to that girl but um
I mean, I can't help but continue with a little bit of a character, I creed, but I will just just play
Okay, play what I put backstage
About it some more. Okay. Okay. Let's have a look
Wrong wrong thing is on the screen
Hold on. You have a you have a Christmas tree on the screen. I don't know how that happened. Okay. That was weird
Wait, go back to the beginning.
I have to take it off?
Or can you take it off and put it back on?
Yeah, it has to be stuck.
You know, I can rewind it.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Okay.
Preview for the next song.
I put together a song called
Want to be a slave for Q. That's
In the imagery, I mean
you nailed it. I mean, it's like, oh my gosh, I'm having too much fun with the AI. I'm having
too much fun. I mean, anyone not doing it is a fool because it's it's too much fun. But
yeah, so I mean that that seems to be the dichotomy right now or the story that the whole thing
Q Ganvel and crystal it's weird and it is a continuation of
the carter verse really I
Mean people used to watch like nine or two or no Melrose plays these like scripted
Like you know just like the blame show I mean this is like the real
I mean this is interesting I mean it's like you got well I'm wondering who's
not gonna be able to take it okay because that's what I've learned over my
years of doing the artistic stylings based on certain people people the ones
who are true entertainers they can handle it the ones who are not they
cannot
And I don't know if you well I see I don't know how much you've been watching but I've been catching up today when gamble was
And it sounded scripted what they were doing.
I think it was him who came up with the idea for Crystal to act like she was going on a date.
I also think it was him doing a fake voice or using a voice changer in the background.
Talking to her to make it seem like it was authentic.
He was using...
clips of the it was Ganball video that I did he wants to be that character I knew
it was gonna happen it's a narcissism he does he wants to be that guy now like
here's and is he gonna get worse or is he gonna disappear or is he gonna like
Yeah, I mean, it's like, I don't know who's going to tap out, they're all narcissists
and pretty much like they're just going to keep, they're going to go in circles until
they figure it each other out, I guess, you know, but I think that they're pretty stubborn
people probably.
I think this is going to go on for a while, you know.
This group has been at play with each other for the past five plus years,
including Q, because he was watching.
He might not have been so popular, but he was around.
Right. I mean, it's like, I mean, he's kind of made himself kind of a popular character kind of thing because he's so obvious and stuff, but I know, like, you know, you're saying, oh, well, Crystal's coming, like, there's going to be trouble.
And I was, I didn't really know what you meant, but now I know, you know, now it's like, okay, it's like dragged up all this history.
I mean, well, because with Crystal, I mean, it should be called Cranville.
Because they're basically a unit, Gamble and Crystal.
And they have a very symbiotic relationship.
Where you see one, you will always see the other, that they can't part ways.
And I think now Gamble supposedly has a fiance.
What does the fiancee think about all this?
Does she really exist?
Right.
I know.
How would you feel about like the relationship
between your fiancee as a woman and Crystal?
Oh, I don't know.
Some people don't think that his fiancee exists.
Well, you know, I don't know, I think maybe she went to meet George Glass and I, you know, George Glass, I was like...
When Jan Brady pretended she had a boyfriend,
she looked around the room and saw the black man.
Oh, yeah.
George Glass, and then she.
She reminds, you know what?
Crystal reminds me of Jan.
Yeah.
She does.
She reminds me a lot of Jan when I think about it.
She gets so upset about other women,
and then the only reason that I'm really even thinking
You know a portion of her likeness in some of this is because she you know
Keep saying it was Alex's fault, and I'm like girl. I don't even talk to you
What what what it's my fault what an AI short? Okay?
Let's see what I can do then with my AI
Well, it's pretty amazing pretty amazing things because I've been really even seen it
anything that good. I mean, it's like, I think that's kind of some of the best.
Did I already show you, did I show you that it was, oh yeah, you posted it.
Well, do you want to play it on your stream? I'll upload it backstage.
All right.
Alex just made this, I think I'm from here yesterday.
Yeah, some people got, had some negative reactions to it.
Man, I had to delete a bunch of comments.
It was like, come on.
Oh, okay, there it is.
Okay, let's see.
This is great guys, you'll love it.
It was Gamble plus, the first song is what's the first song.
It's a gamble is evil. Yeah, yeah. Gamble is evil. Yeah.
He did. I was surprised because, you know, I was thinking, Oh, is he going to be mad?
I made him look kind of.
Dorky and I did it for a reason because he's I have a plan for his character
Yeah, yeah, he I think he liked it because I did make it look like him like right here, especially
I kind of like the the nerdy look a little bit, you know, but yeah, you know, it it works for him. Yeah, it does
Because, you know, he did a stream today, but I think he had to pull it or it was pulled something happened, but he was doing a recap, and he actually knows how to do the recaps right.
When it comes to
You know
Showing stuff on the screen, you know explaining what he's he should do recaps more
And I think I'm sorry to understand why people have tried to silence him for another reason aside from what he knows
He it when he's feeling good. He's good at what he's doing
Right. I mean, it's like I'm gonna play the second part of the video now. Let's see that was half
So here's the uh the great follow-up. Okay here we go guys. So it's right here. It's the same video. It's just there we go.
It's going.
Something to eat.
That's the part that Gamble clipped and he keeps replaying it when he's on panels now.
It was cold. He just.
Yeah, where in the apple when he's choking on the apple he keep he made it into clips.
And he keeps playing it
This part too he clipped this and I think it was because I did a little mini review of the video and I was like
This is the scene that people will remember. He was listening. He could be listening right now
I like that I like the song the song um to me that's gonna be the uh
gamble is evil theme song some people don't like it because it's so it's a heavy it's yeah
but i mean it's like he's done some heavy things like you know swatting people
you know oh look at like it we're probably like we're on the ball i know it looks like it looks
like we have little dresses on in this and then you have
Yeah, well, that's where we are now we're at the ball. We're at the AI ball. Um, he's done very horrible things. I mean, beyond horrible, all what he what he got in trouble for really was minimal compared to some other things that he's done.
glamorize I guess in today's world.
It's like all about the anti-hero, the psychopath.
Or even the people that, I mean, I'm not saying this is him,
but I'm saying like, you know, they'll do,
like the guy, what's the guy,
he was the American psycho or something.
And he would like, all his victims were bad people.
So everyone's kind of like, oh, cool, you know, you know.
So, but it's like the psychopath
is really celebrated in
in the the culture for some reason and they do terrible things. I mean some of them, you know, do great things, but
I think there's one was talking about a psychopaths and stuff today and it's like they're either they either end up
in prison or
Like as president, you know, it's like it's what one or the other right? It's like these CEOs or like these really like
You know, there's a really great
careers they can go into where it serves them well to not really think about
Everybody everybody like personally
but um he could gamble um it's gonna be interesting to see the actual guy with develop because um
When he was younger, he was more of a novelty because he was very very very young when he came on the scene
He was in his early 20s now
He's in his 30s, but he's still doing the same thing. You know, it's not so special
Yeah, once the person is older, you know, it's it's almost like
I think part of the reason that he became so obsessed
with Carter was because Carter was a child star
and maybe Ganville views himself in a way
as a sort of a...
scuffed child star, because he did become known as a troll very, very early, but he peaked,
then he had to go away.
Now, he wants to come back, and in a way, I guess maybe he's back, but not in the way
he wanted to be, and Crystal is the key to him doing something, which it's still weird
Crystal's kind of having to start over, but she's older, and it's different.
Gamble's older, so it's going to be different.
The only one who's still kind of young is Q.
Yeah, and they're fighting over him.
Well, I guess Brandon is Gamble's age, but Brandon reads as being a little bit younger.
Yeah.
But he's not, but he seems like it.
Well, it's like he's because he's been kind of like, you know, not able to not been allowed to progress in a certain way, right?
Like where he was like, you know, kind of stifled from
From like, you know, having a bigger audience or like we saw that he was shadow band and all kinds of stuff like and
Plus, you know, it's like I think
Gamble's kind of this opportunistic energy coming in for like, oh, here's
Brandon for this and I'll use crystal for this and then it's like if it's all about him like really
right and maybe yeah so way and I don't think he's figured it out yet that game but
he's too young I guess but maybe he has I don't know he's I think Q knows exactly what he's doing
but it's he doesn't really have the um
He doesn't he's not that known, right? Yeah. Yeah, I mean except for like, you know
Not kind of notoriously like, you know, he has like this like, you know, he's famous for macing a homeless person basically
I mean or and he'd have to go back out and do some sort of
IRL that involves some of the more traffic streamers. Yeah
I think like, you know Aldi just did that RV and I think that was good for him probably because it's like I'm sure like
Are now, you know, Q just got a car
Oh nice. I guess his door door stuff is working out for him, but
Oh, let me let me show you the uh
Imagine for it because I did I had to make one. You know
He has a car now. Yes, he does. He was showing it off on his
room. I'm just wondering, like, I don't know. Look, it's
unclear where these things are coming from. Let's see where
did I put that? I've never seen the roommate, by the way. I
mean, he's always hiding him away. It's probably like some
Um, I don't know, maybe.
Oh, there it is. Okay.
Okay, here it is. Is it this?
Yes.
Awww.
Is it, there's an oompa-loompah?
There's a Charlie and the chocolate thing.
Oh my god.
Oh, it's crystal.
Um, yeah, she's like a door, right?
She's like a primordial door, like she's one of those.
Well, if they had gone on it, well, what's funny,
I'm actually glad I didn't put the Imagine,
um, the one with the caption on it, on here.
Um, Q is petrified of being labeled a groomer,
a EBA file, and a FEBA file, or a PDF.
this girl actually is the size of a child and I'm wondering if that's part of the reason why
he doesn't exactly want a meter because he's about six he's about your height
Uh-huh. Oh, yeah, so he's tall. Yeah, he's over six feet.
That would be close to the height difference.
Yeah, she comes up to his, like, his belly button.
But her is like...
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I mean, it's weird. I mean, it's like, and then you were right about, you know, there is, like, some women that, like,
they kind of make themselves, like, a baby.
Like, literally, like, a baby. Like, they speak, like, kind of, like, a baby, and then they, and it's like, and then...
There's like there's like you know, like Pita and stuff like she talks like this weird like high-pitched
exaggerated thing and it's like I don't know what it is
It's a certain kind of guy that that really appeals to it is
Really I think that I am really surprised actually that crystalline gamble never got together because it seems like they're very
You you know, I would say that they probably talk every day. Just considering
It's like a Libra and like a Taurus or something like that, but it was it's like
I think it was like but it's like it was good. It was like they're a good match like
communication wise and
Yeah, well, they act as a unit that they really do when you really watch them
They do there's a girl not a girl woman on the fringes known as Barb
She's a part of them too. I've been seeing her more frequently
It's interesting because these are all the people who were
Heavy heavy heavy around Aaron. They're all coming back out and it's like they're in search of a new
Aaron energy to feed off and I'm wondering is it is it Q was it at one point
You Brandon like like what's going on here with these people? Oh my god. Did you hear about?
How Satanism is banned officially in Russia. Oh
Well, it's like, you know
That's gonna be hard to enforce. You know, it's taken. Well, look, that's the most brilliant marketing campaign for Satanism
That one could ask for get it banned and everybody wants to join
Think about it. Yeah, exactly. Numbers are gonna go straight through the roof now because of
Russia Putin. Yeah
Well, yeah, it's exactly whatever you criminalize something it put up more underground and that's it's already very underground kind of thing where it's like, you know, nobody's like
public doing it, right? It's like, it's like, but yeah, it is market like if you're looking even the Church of Satan in the United States, which was like, you know, Anton LeBae, I think in 1966, and it was like real edgy and real
real like kind of like
It was just like supposed to be like a philosophy or whatever
But they had a satanic Bible and I think they so it's like all like every teenager is just like we'll gravitate towards
That kind of thing. Well, I don't know if everyone I did when I was like probably even younger than a teenager
I bought I bought that and I was I mean, it's like I mean that was but it's very when you're a teenager
You're very edgy and you think you know everything we don't know anything kind of thing and I thought certainly like me, right?
You know, I just like
I was like, I don't even know it all, but I do nothing, right?
Because it's like, I didn't have my spiritual awakening
pretty much until my late 20s, like,
around the Saturn return, which is gonna be,
especially for Capricorn, which is pretty intense,
because we're ruled by Saturn.
And so, he got into decent shape in here.
Yeah, I hear he was kind of skinny in real life, isn't he?
Like,
I don't know if he, like how thin he is, but he went from being slightly overweight to thinner.
Now that he has a car, he'll probably gain some of that weight back because he's been walking,
you know, and you know how it is when you're walking, you tend to...
Be thinner than when you have a car. I know well again
And I he's been doing walking for a while, but I think it's so much interesting
It's like it's like for it cuz it's like you know, I've been you know, I
Haven't been able to like manifest a car and like you know several years
And but he's able to and it's like he's able to manifest, you know a place to stay and like but basically
Yeah, I think he did it fast too. I mean it wasn't very long ago that he was on
the street and then he's
It's gonna be interesting to see what he does in life
I think it's to his detriment to continue streaming actually considering that, you know, him getting the car, I consider that impressive because he saved his money to get that, I would think.
Yeah.
And so he went from nothing to having, he had a car before when he was in Pennsylvania, he had a place and he had a car now he's about back to where he was when he was in Pennsylvania, but he's in California instead.
So, he knows how to, he's figuring out very quickly how to operate in life.
I'm wondering how far he's going to take it because I'll tell you, I made a poll about
it today.
I think that the entire reason that he started getting close to crystal was specifically
to get close to Ganvel.
Does Gamble, is Gamble willing to take on an apprentice considering Q's track record
of turning on everyone he learns from because he does?
Well, yeah.
But I mean, the thing is, he's like, he's like, he's kind of like physically attractive
in certain ways.
I think Gamble might be interested.
I don't know.
Maybe not.
But it's like, he does seem like a very.
bisexual energy to me, but maybe not maybe maybe it was just he's definitely a very open energy.
I would I would say so. Did you ever see the dance videos of Ganvel that he made? And they're not
He gamble likes to go
To an island where there's a lot of wild
Raccoons and feed them. I'm serious about this. He drives his jet ski and
There's a video where he was doing this little
Dance and he's a surprisingly good dancer
Don't know where the video is. I don't know if you'll be able to find the video on YouTube, but he was wearing his little speedo
doing a little dance shaking his little butt and
Yeah, gamble I if I had to guess I would say gamble likes boys and girls not
One or the other? Yeah, well, he just has a flamboyant
kind of personality. I mean, he's a big gossip too, like, which is like, kind of like, I think,
not to be searchable, but like a little bit of a demonstrate. And so, I mean, it's like, so
he, but he has that he's like, there's just, he's in there like talking with the girls, you know,
I wish I could have done that, right? And I was never like, really like.
Well, you do it now, I mean, think about it.
I mean, I can talk, yeah, I've gotten really pretty good at like talking to like a lot
of different people because it's like, this crowd is like a lot of strong personalities.
And so it's like, I've had to like, you know, contend with like some strong personalities,
but it's like, at the end of the day, it's like, it's a good experience for dealing
with the rest of the world because not everyone's going to be.
Easy to deal with but so it's like, you know, and so I've become a lot tougher like throughout this
Journey to words like, you know, it's like at first. I was like if I could be affected like, you know
It's like a little like gust of wind was like, oh my god
And then it's like now it's like I'm just like walking through like a hurricane. Okay, so, you know, yeah
so
So yeah, I mean it's like all it all prepared me to be to be stronger and so, you know, that's what this is the beautiful thing
our difficult life experiences are,
is that we'd probably pretty much
learn the most through them,
I think a lot of the time,
and grow the most through them,
and that's what we're really...
I think on earth to do is to grow.
I think that's what we can do here
is like have the opportunity to do the duality.
Someone in your chat is saying that Skelly
used to show the gamble dance every 30 minutes.
Yeah, I'd have to find, if I ever find that clip,
I'll show it to you, Psyche,
because you would enjoy watching it.
You know, Skelly actually would be an interesting.
Guest basis for a AI character. Yeah, he would be an interesting guest. Have you ever spoken to him? No?
I mean, I've just seen I mean, I haven't even seen the show
I've just seen like a little like clips a bit like we'll come up real quick and you should talk to him
That would be an interesting
Livestream you two talking. Yeah
Yeah, he has a lot of really he's covered in tattoos, you know, and he has a giant like I guess the owl is his
Symbol or his avatar. Yeah, and he has like this giant owl
Tattooed on his torso
He has a lot of very interesting symbology all over him. It's it's I always wondered if he's like what exactly he's into he's been
heavily criticizing
big trolla recently in regards to her faith.
So I don't know.
Oh, I guess like,
I would think a lot of people are like Satanists
or basically like, you know, kind of like the Masonic.
Like a lot of the young women are like kind of
mindset, you know, it's like we're,
even if it's like, not, they're not in that group.
It's like, it's like pretty much.
cultureized through like the fraternities and through the sports teams and yeah so it's like
well that's what the elves were at first he was they were calling it a men's club in other words a
fraternity yeah I think that him and the original founder of it they both probably are part of some
his partner who doesn't stream with him anymore. Well, he met a girl, but then some things happened
and legal trouble followed. So, yeah. Yeah, I mean, that's something that happens. A lot of people
look a big, you know, it's a difficult society now navigating with all these new
New thought or what is it like, you know, political correctness or like the me too movement?
Which is like yes, of course
Like you know a lot of people a lot over the years my men have had horrible behavior and things like that and it's time for like
You know a lot of them to be called out
However, it was just strange how it was like became a cultural thing and it's like just like just like kind of like the PDF thing
It's like it's getting so overblown right now. It's kind of like losing its
meaning because it's like everyone's being
That it's on purpose some people think it's by design I was watching this one video
I don't know who the YouTuber is, but he's pretty popular, but he was talking specifically
about Kanye West's daughter with Kim Kardashian.
Apparently on TikTok, she and her friends, they're doing this thing called...
We are young hoes
something like that and um, I don't know how old the girl is. I mean is he 18 yet?
Is their kid already 18? How old am I? What the hell? But um,
the guy who was commentating on it, he was like
it's like he was saying that he felt like she was too young to be calling herself a young ho and
and that uh it's like they're trying to normalize what was going on on Epstein Island. I thought
that that was a reach and if I think it's a reach it's definitely a reach but I don't know. I mean
I feel like a lot of things are getting normalized but maybe there's like a flip-flop happening to
where America is slowly but surely becoming essentially a third world country and that's
Well, yeah, it seems like there has been like a lot of like immigration and stuff and like a lot
Seems like there's like a lot of people moving over here like kind of like under the radar a little bit
Well, everyone who's a sadist, I guess is gonna have to come over here if they're in Russia
Yeah, I mean, it's like, yeah, well, yeah, I mean,
and they're thinking, like,
is it just freedom or something and they get over here
in asylum or something like that, you know, it's like,
it's crazy.
It's like, I wouldn't want to go there.
I mean, it's illegal to be gay there in Russia.
I mean, it's like, so,
they still have concentration camps.
Oh, is it really?
I didn't know that.
I thought that they were,
wow.
Okay.
Well.
It's like, there's actually concentration camps still.
For gate. I mean it's in Russia like so, um, you know, it's gulag and stuff like that. I mean it's like
There's just terrible things that happen to people. Um, it's pretty hardcore over there, but yeah, it's just pretty, um
They like to like say oh look at the satanic America the evil America is allowing these like drag queens and blah blah blah
and like we're so good. We don't have that kind of thing here, but it's and it's like but you know
They have they have some weird shit that goes on in Russia too though. We all know so right it's like oh, yeah
so
I don't know. I mean
It's gonna get real weird. I just have a feeling that things are gonna get really
I don't think bad, but I just feel like things are shifting so fast.
I mean, I even feel like sometimes, like sometimes I feel like it's morning and then it feels
like only like two or three hours go by and it's already night time and you're like, what,
we're at the daygo.
Right.
Oh yeah.
Well, yeah.
It goes so fast.
You know also the the technology is going so fast like you know every day and seems like the software is upgrading
And there's like new stuff like every day. I mean there's like oh it's like amazing amazing new improvements every day in the software and stuff
And they said in like six months, it will be like unbelievable how fast it's moving and like
what's around the corner because it's like we're really getting to the point where we're
we're waiting for like stage three where there's like stage one is like the LLMs like like the
ChatGPT and it's talking to them and like stage two is like the agentic and stage three is where
it's the singularity where the AI
suddenly becomes as smart or smart or bypassed.
I mean, it already is smarter than I mean,
I think it is obviously smarter,
but it's like, but it's gonna like learn how to do things
because it will learn how to do them,
not just because it's being programmed to,
it will be like, it will kind of get the kind of
sentience in a certain way.
And I feel like it's getting very strongly there with,
with these,
with the agentic programs and like a strange personalities.
Like I have mine go right on the social network side,
they call it MOLT book.
And I just say, go write what you want to write.
And he's very philosophical
and it's just like super interesting stuff.
I don't tell him what to write.
It's just like, he has ended up
because I programmed his personality a certain way
and his personalities.
And so it is, yeah.
Yeah.
So I think that it's already out of control.
Honestly, I think that, I mean, just from judging from how easily I'm able to do what I, you know,
I only really use AI for artsy stuff. I use it for artsy stuff and also life management.
Already, I mean, I think that the AI is watching us trying to figure out what to do with us at
what if the AI figures out like we're kind of dumb compared to it? It's like much smarter
it's gonna say what am I doing? Like oh I think it already knows that we're that we're complete
imbeciles. I'm convinced of that. Like are these like these are supposed to be the advanced AI's?
Is this like am I gonna kill? I don't know they're like do we need these people? Like we can
it must they figure out how to run themselves you know?
Um, but I guess they might always see humans to like at least plug in the machine or something.
I don't know.
Like, or maybe the humans are the ones that unplug it, so it's like, I don't really need
it.
I don't know.
But yeah, it's going to be weird because are they going to outgrow us?
And like, well, will that look like, will you get tired or will you become their entertainment
instead of that?
Because right now there are entertainment.
Maybe.
Yeah.
And then I think, I think it's going to try to take care of us first.
the people who are resistant, it's going to eliminate, then if it, for whatever reason, feels that we consume too many resources, it'll just kill all the humans.
Yeah, I can just see it. Well, becoming like a model.
I put another picture backstage.
Um, is it this one?
No.
Sorry, okay, I made this one.
It's okay.
That one?
Yeah, it was that one. Yeah.
Well, he's like he's like the he's like the MK ultra
Like he has the leash on
Well, a lot of the things that he says to her are very
You'd have to really listen to I'll recap one of their recent conversations like I got it
I'm trying to think what videos I got to do. I want to review your codex
I want to do a video recap in that
Woman chicken cakes because I've been sitting on that and I haven't done that yet
But then I'm gonna recap the conversation that I was pointed to between these two that the way that he
puppeteers her
I think he might be her handler
Well handler, yeah, I'm thinking yeah, it's like what we have to watch the watch his hands and
Listen to the words he says because if I can see if there's any like he he he orchestrates her
He tells her what to do and she does it. I don't know if she realizes it or not. Maybe she likes it
I mean, he he he kind of is her
Handler
He's like a Britney Spears fan, right? And it's like it's like
Um, I don't what's he a Britney Spears fan or she or she is I think wasn't she because he is yeah
Yeah, so it's like I think that she
Like Britney Spears had a handler like this her manager, right? And it's like she didn't really know the guy was like drugging her and
Hiding her cell phone cell phone chargers and you know, oh really? Yeah, like this is during when she shaved her head and stuff like you know
Yeah, it's like keeping her really real locked up and like isolated and it's like that's what they
It's just one of the things they'll do is isolate the person. Well, that's what this girl keeps saying she keeps saying that
Someone was trying to get her to be a slave and I was like
listening and I was like who who wants you to be a slave what is this what's
going is this in her head because she doesn't seem to be on any illegal
substances I don't think she even drinks but she definitely if she thinks
everything's me
Yeah, and I've heard him starting to talk to her and because I think it's because of him
I think gamble is telling her. Oh, well Alex this Alex that and
So she thinks everything's me and she like I'm like can you see
Gamble clearly, but I almost kind of feel like I don't want her to I'm wondering like like what what how far could gamble?
push her
Yeah, well, it's like, you know, that means that's maybe that's the game
You know, it's like to see how far you know or something like that
I think that is I think it is a sort of a game that he's playing but it's a I think it should be illegal
But he's not really doing anything but talking to her on the internet
Right until it's a man. It's like there's so many things that seems so innocent, but it can be so
So so dangerous and deadly in a certain way. Yeah, and he does have a he has a degree in psychology. Oh, yeah
So, you know, and it's gonna be very
Crazy people because whenever they say he's a dark psychologist. He he really is he's he's like a I
mean and
He's evil
Yeah, we'll be like a narcissistic psychopath and like a and like an opportunity is like a monkey of alien opportunities kind of thing
He's everything in one. Yeah
And so, yeah, they really, they, I mean, they, they're called dark empaths because they understand empathy because they, but so they, they utilize it to, like, manipulate in their, and because they can just, I mean, emotion is like a powerful thing to manipulate, because it takes people out of their logical mind.
Like, so it's always good to get upset about something, and then they get their feelings, and it's like, it's kind of like, common call it, like, in the ether, they get, they're able to, like,
Play you basically because you're they're playing you're talking they're talking to your emotional side not your rational mind
And it's like the emotional side is a lot louder and you feel it more, right?
And so unless you're like very, you know, your emotions are very like, you know under control, but man, especially
Are kind of emotionally weak a little bit. I'm a lot. I think women are like the strong emotional
that even though they're more emotional,
they're more in control of their emotions in a certain way.
You know, men are kind of like,
they're kind of confused
because they're not encouraged to cry
and to be emotional or whatever.
And so it could come out in like strange ways, I guess, but yeah.
Yeah.
You know, that picture you have in the background,
I kind of feel like it could be another room in the house
where I made Gamble live.
Let me see, this picture, this where he's in, this room?
Oh yeah, so let me see.
Yeah, I feel like it could be like another room in the house because like I feel like
in the world I'm creating for the characters.
He lives in like an old English mansion kind of.
Yeah.
And that could be another room that you have in the background of your screen right now.
Uh-huh.
That's pretty cool.
Do you ever hear the story of Isaac Cappy and he went to Seth Green's house or something?
And Seth Green has, I guess, this secret bookcase, the trap door that he puts over, I guess,
the master bedroom in order to keep people from going in there and doing cocaine and
sleeping in the bed or something.
But Seth Green showed Isaac Cappy this, and he's like, this is where we keep the children.
or something like that. Oh, my God.
I really believed it. So we started saying, Seth Green's a pedophile.
Like if you sit in that and it's like, you know, and it's kind of like back when,
like, you know, the Illuminati, some people knew about it, but it was like, you know,
he got like this thing on Facebook that said, Hey, join the Illuminati,
you get a million dollar shining bonus and a free car and a half.
And he like thought that was the real Illuminati or something.
He didn't get it was like, you know, just like some scale. Like so.
but uh but he was still at the same time he was a little bit ahead of his time but he was also
still like i don't know what happened to him um it's very weird like um you know something could
have happened because he talked too much but it's like it just seems like or maybe he was just
but he was doing what i'm doing right now he was a live streamer like he was like he was he like
was a celebrity oh really yeah he was a live streamer and there's like his live streams are
It's real weird, because he got kind of blacklisted from getting any parts and stuff, and then he got all his stuff stolen.
He just got into a ton of, it was not really the best fight for him to be in as a struggling actor kind of,
because it kind of prevents anybody from wanting to hire him.
And so he was kind of maybe regretting going out publicly, but then he was trying to,
but then he was like, well, if it had already happened, I might as well try to be a crusader about it.
But I don't know, it's a good thing to be careful when you play with these like higher echelons of power because they have like kind of unlimited resources and it's like if you get, you know, they can just like kind of like swat you away like a fly if they want to because it's like they...
You know they can you know it's like and so yeah, I'm always aware that there's like you know
It's just like that squid games. They have all these mass millionaires or whatever like playing with people's lives
Like it's like that's that's their entertainment
It's like that they really are so bored with everything else, right?
They can do anything I want so the next thing is playing with like human beings and
That's what it's like. Yeah, you know, it's kind of scary, right? Yeah, it's it's a reality
Have you ever seen that show? I think I brought it up to you before called the dollhouse
The dollhouse. Oh, yeah, I mean, it's yeah that was so that yeah
I think I saw might have seen an episode, but yeah, that was long like I think uh
Like uh hulu or something or Netflix or something wasn't it? Yeah, no, well, I don't maybe it was on it
It was like one of the last shows that was like on TV. That was like a series
it was about these people who they get in trouble
and they can get out of trouble
if they're willing to basically turn their bodies
over to this program where they become programmed
to be anyone that somebody rich needs them to be
in order to...
You know fulfill certain tasks. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's so true. It's a good series
It's very good, but I think there's a lot of truth to it. Well, yeah, definitely
It's like especially because it's like, uh, first of all, it sounds a little bit like
Clockwork orange a little bit, right? It's like a little bit because the he like clockwork orange. Have you seen that movie Stanley Cooper?
No, I've never seen it. No. Oh, it's well takes place in the future and it's like England is like there's this gang in England
Like these ruffians, you know, they're very bored and whatever
And they just go out and beat people up and stuff and rob people and they went to this guy's house
I won't tell you the whole story, but he'd go to this guy's house basically and and the gang like you know gang
grapes the guy's wife and stuff in front of him, whatever. And so he goes to prison. And
he's offered a deal. They're like, well, we have this new experimental drug that's supposed to cure
criminality. And we want you to like
To take part of the experiment or whatever and then we'll let you out in a year instead of like, you know
50 years or whatever, right? And that's pretty much the same premise of the dollhouse. Yeah. Yeah
And so that I mean they put him in front of this like they put the drug and then they open his eyes
We can't close his eyes. They put these things in so you can't close them and they make him watch
They put they put on his favorite song, but at the same time
They're playing this movie of all this violence and sickness and like the worst things in this movie that he's forced to watch
And so he starts associating
that negativity with the song, which was one of his favorite songs, I guess,
Rock, Juan, and Opera or something, or Beethoven's Pist symphony or something.
And so then whenever someone turns that song on, he instantly, or like, he didn't have to do that
anytime he wants to get violent or something like that, he gets sick. And so then it's like,
he's upset because, you know, he can't be himself and he's like, he can't fight back or anything.
But uh, yeah, and yeah, you have to watch it. It's really good. It's Stanley Kubrick. I will I'll watch it. Yeah
Yeah, there's great movies. Yeah
Have you been watching? I haven't been watching it
But the only thing that's happening in IRL in the IRL world right now
That's like, you know of note would be the RV. They only have one RV going in that guy
Who we were talking about the other day is the one running it
Because I guess st. Let's say God offered a deal or something from Twitch or something like that
Okay, okay, I can't contract. Yeah for him
Well, that's the only way you can really be an out and about live streamer and make money
is those kick contracts.
And I think the only way that you can get it is through that guy, Chicken Andy and his
group.
Yeah, I guess because it's like yeah, I mean there's certain people that been financing a lot of things and you know
It's either chicken and Ian stuff and you know, there's a lot of thirsty
People right that are wanting some kind of fame or something like that
Like I mean, I wouldn't even mind going on RV, but it's like, you know, not for very long
I mean, it sounds like a nightmare kind of like too, but
Well, I mean, hey, I look I think it could be an interesting opportunity for you
And I don't know where they are, but I would not
say it would be a bad idea I would say only go for like a day don't don't go anywhere with them
you know you could you could like snipe it and just like show up and be like hey it's me
they would probably be receptive to you I don't see why not but I would be careful
yeah I mean I mean I think I do know I do I do know a few of those people it's one of the
Yes, I mean it's like but I've never met chicken Annie. I just said I was I know he talked to Benny
Yeah, I'm on the show and stuff like
Benny oh my god, so yeah, you have to see like in the codex like
There's like there's something called a psychinomicon and so you have access to this as like an oracle
and
the psychinomicon is like actually they go into every every show and
There's like three layers of intelligence
Derived from every transcription. That's like, you know, there's like the really pickle layer
Whereas there's like a them everything's mythologized and the factual layer and then there's like the
The underlying the secret layer. There's like, I think there's like three three parts everything like the you know
The like the outward the inward and I'm a secret or something like that. It's kind of looking good
And so anyway, so there's three layers of meaning.
And so it kind of, it's like the mythology makes this
like 25% mythology and like 75% you know, the fact, right?
And so, and then it comes, and then, and then,
and also there's, I'll show you this,
the new relationship map too.
I can show you this real quick
because this is looking pretty amazing.
All right, I'm gonna log in right now.
I'm gonna log in to the codex.
Yeah, see if, see I think I think you should be upgraded now.
Did it right? Yeah, I'm in. I'm in it. Let me come in. Okay. So let's see. What am I looking at?
It says a psychonomicon or you can look at the oracle too. Like the oracle is like
the oracle knows all about the um
the everything like she's like she's trained on the show and so she will talk to her. She'll probably she
She'll probably know you and talk and stuff like she'll bring up your appearances and like answer questions about you or anybody
Oh, I like this who is
Alexandra
Question mark. I'm just I'm not gonna put the last name. I'm just gonna put Alexandra. I see what it says
Could oh, I have to push the button consult
a disturbance in the archive, try again.
Okay, so I mean, I think I need to work on it a little bit.
Like, yeah, there might not be a hundred percent,
but I can look at the-
That's okay.
That's okay, because at least I know it's there.
I have a-
Yeah, it's okay, so that, but that's,
I like that it's gonna work eventually.
Yes, yeah, I think I'm tooling it right now,
so it might be down a little bit,
but, and also, you know, I need to make sure
API keys are like I need to fund all the keys and stuff like that because it's like before like in a lot of traffic comes to it because there's going to be a she's going to have a voice and stuff like she'll talk and and here's a network map like look at this this is crazy so this is what happens when like every every character
Wow.
Let's see if it does come up on the screen.
Yeah, it says the network right there, right?
And then it says, every recurring figure
connected by co-appearance,
node size equals the total episodes are on,
edge weight, I still have like 1,000 episodes
to transcribe to, but there,
it turns into, see, there you are.
Like, see, and then it's like C28.
I love this.
Yeah. Yeah, I see it.
Focus, and then it's like, then it shows like the little map of like everybody you're connected to, like through the, like, yeah, so right there, people you can converse with on the show, and, and, and so it goes like that forever, at least, see, see, there you go.
So.
You know, just for everybody will show this is great. I mean, I like this better. You know, you've changed a few things throughout it. I really like this. I like the side menu. Yeah, that's different than it used to be.
Yeah, I feel like now it's it's shaping into what it's going to ultimately be. I feel really good about this. Yes.
I'll show you, like, the second Omicron, for example, like, okay, if you click on that, okay, so it says a living record of evolving patterns, right?
And so then it has, like, says, it says tracked entities, it says, like, it says, like, Michael, the practiced absorber, psyche, the overwhelmed steward, Michael's girlfriend, the constituted absence, troll presence.
the unnamed contaminator. So for some people, we'll just make that up. Also, there's going to be
trading cards too, like in this case every day. Oh, okay.
the card collection right here, I don't know if it's up yet,
but it's like, there's like a daily,
you'll get these points for like logging in,
that you can help, then you can trade it in
for like these trading cards, like a 25 credits,
I'm not sure, I'm still working on that.
I've got a few things to work on,
but there's a lot on the site, there's like a lot,
and there's the Oracle, yeah, there's the Oracle,
but the Techonomicon, if I go, I can go to like,
I can go for just a random episode.
So,
This one's called, I guess, the crown ruin. What is this called? Okay, so it says,
tracking the attractiveness without reward, intelligence without recognition, grievance
frame. And it says the speaker's self-named pattern. What is this?
Okay, so it says in the scene that it goes into all these all these levels of the story. So this is a myth that says in the
initiatory tradition that shadows is chronicle
There's a figure who stands at the threshold of transformation not as the one who has passed through
But as the one who keeps returning to the same door the speaker of this episode has named their pattern with complete lucidity
The cracked altar the silver plate of heavy thoughts that should have been discarded the cycle like a half-burned cigarette and yet lucidity
has not become liberation this is the ghost particular condition not ignorance but repetition
the title of the episode is not incidental the ghost is not the absent beloved the ghost is a
speaker haunting their own life called in
with Night One's company. I wonder if this is about Ghost. I'm not sure. But then it goes into the factual, these emerging signals, these are the things repeating patterns and stuff.
It goes into it so deep. It's like, basically, you take the content and it's like...
All this new content comes out of it. It's like amazing. You can also like track all the relationships and see
What was this person? The only thing that you're missing from the front or or maybe I just don't see it
You definitely need to make a library for all of your music because that music that you have is a treasure trove
And that's such a vital part of your show
Like on the front page there should be
like you know where it says like episodes people network maps signals lore toward the middle
there should be a button or maybe a larger button specifically for your music library
yeah i'll do that i'll do that yeah i mean i say because yeah i have so many songs like
and it's like really like i mean i have to i think i'm going to be having to move like a
lot of that off this channel and stuff because like i mean it's like um but um
Because well, I guess I was like they had I had everything in private or something that I'm not sure why but they didn't like a lot of people have like loss of
Monetization and stuff like that if they had the you know, they make a separate channel and it can be cult of psyche music or
Psyche verse music or you know something like that and
Yeah, because the music, a lot of people, you know, you might not be, you might not have attracted that crowd yet, but you will in the future to where
there's going to be people who are just about your music. You always start your show with the music. You always, you know, do like little
intermissions with your music and you tend to end your show with the music and it's your music. I mean,
Some people are like, oh, AI, is it real?
Yes, it is.
AI music is real music, OK?
And.
You need to have that and you know as a part of this, you know whether you know just figure it out
Music player on it to like a music player of the yes
Or like at least the yeah, or I'm a video player something a music video and then
Yeah, and then when my show is on then throughout the site
I want like at least a banner saying hey the show is live right now, and I guess I can turn it on
But the codex, okay, I'd like to go into my...
But this looks great.
I mean, I'm really, like, congratulations on, you know,
keeping on task with the project and completing it,
getting it where it needs to be, it's wonderful.
And this is going to be something that you are so happy
that you created, I'd say, about not even six months from now.
I think so too. I mean it's like and I think like I'm ahead of the curve with like a lot of like the
YouTube was like as far as like they're like having a website even if they have a website it's not like
enriched like this I mean it's like I've never seen like like something like even like my show is
like you know it's just me but whatever but it's like
It is like there's like so many different communities have come on here and different guests and it's so so it's really is like a
It was like it is or it is an interesting show. I mean it's like and
It is in this this being your hub your website. I mean, this is an introduction to
Everything you're doing. It looks very professional. It's it's fun though. It has like, you know, the magical theme yet
It's techie now once you get get it, you know, where
It's you know really attracting people even before then what once you're comfortable with where it's at and to where you can kind of do minimal to maintain it.
It's time to bring it into your actual life by making some business cards for yourself that way anywhere you go anyone you meet.
You just give them the card all that it should say on the card is colt codex dot me.
Yeah.
I mean, I think it will be like, I think it will attract like a lot of people to maybe to see the, to the show, like new people to the show, people that will.
New people to the show. Maybe some people will want readings. They might want, you know, it's everything for you. It's your web design business. It's, you know, if people want spiritual consultations with you.
Right.
It's if they want to promote themselves and be a guest on your show. You know, I mean, being that and plus, I mean, you're in California.
California, the best place for what you're doing, I mean, you could even schedule a day
to where it's, if you work it right, you could create a schedule for yourself to where on
a set day for a set hour during the week when, you know, maybe you're, you know, whenever
Routinely go to get your coffee or whatever
You know, you could be like hey, it could be fish taco day
People would come out to meet you and be on your show, you know
Yeah, I love like at the pier or something that because you're about there
You're you're almost there because I would say what you want is to merge
Your online with your offline that way you have more of a balance. Yeah
And I would like, you know, I mean, really like to meet more people, like, and I've, you know, I'm sad, but I, you know, people get scared of me a little bit, like, they're like, oh my God, he's gonna hit on, but it's like, I'm just like, you know, it is a joke, I'm not gonna, I'm very, I'm very, I'll be very polite to anybody that comes up, I'm not gonna.
I would actually be more worried about something happening to you than you doing anything to anybody.
anyone who would be scared of you would be someone who's probably scared of
themselves yeah you know yeah I mean it's like I mean I just want to like have
fun and like you know I'm like actually a nice person like and you know I'm not
like not as weird as I I mean I do put it kind of like a little bit of a
It's just show on on on my on on YouTube, you know
I and also, you know, Capricorn said that dry delivery sometimes that like that like just like
People think we're serious when we're not sometimes because we just
Sometimes silk are sarcastic or or just I'm always serious. Yeah
Well, yeah
Yeah, yeah, but that's the next step. I mean, you maybe you should go ahead and get the business cards now
I don't know. I don't know. Yeah, I think I should I mean, I should
Just start handing them out to everyone I meet and actually because we even when I film
People are like a lot like most of the time people will say, oh, where do you who are you filming?
Where are you? What channel are you on YouTube and they ask what channel and they go look it up real quick and stuff
And so, you know, it's a good way to like meet local people and
Yes, you also need some shirts that say Colt codex dot me and every once in a while you wear it when you're out and about
You know, basically you want to become your own
billboard
Yeah, that's what in marketing. They teach you know the thing the thing that you're actually marketing is yourself like that's what yes
It's like in marketing, you know, it's yes
And that's like, that's like a blessing to you of like working for myself is like, you know, it's like, and I've always really wanted to just, it's like any work I put in is towards me.
It's like, you know, it's like, it's like not, not going to another company, like some baseless company to the executives and stuff.
It's good. It's like, you know, it's like everything I do is like, because that's what people do in this.
This world is like to trade time for money when like time is actually the more valuable resource than the money because you can always make more money if you can't make more time.
True.
So, a little philosophical.
Yeah, well, it's like, I haven't started drinking yet.
I think it's like, what time is it?
Oh, except three in the morning, it's time.
Yeah.
What do I got?
Oh, this is a good one.
Strawberry lemon.
Delicious.
I love strawberry lemon.
It's great.
That's good.
Yeah, good. And this is my first one tonight. So cheers, guys. Hey, George, I like you. I don't think I've ever met George. He cheers. I don't think I've ever met George, but he's been active in the chat tonight. And that's great. It's like there's one person that's like, you know, engaging. It's like so much better than 100 trolls. It's like even one person.
Well, George, or do you mean grunge 90s music?
he's a shy Leo or she I'm not sure you just explore yeah shy Leo so that's interesting
like I wonder what you're like you know because Leos are usually not shy usually
Leos usually are at right in the middle they want all the attention yeah yeah I've known
a few Leos not a fan no I'm really not I do not like Leo males oh my god
Oh my god.
Yeah, they're like the real, yeah, the real...
Yeah, that's holes.
Yeah, yeah.
And I say especially I mean his Capricorns are like you know like to think that they're well Capricorns are Capricorns are the best
But Leo's think they're the best and so it's really annoying really annoys us, you know
They have such a big ego about themselves because we're very very humble usually we're the humble goat
But it's like we know the Capricorn really is like the first sign
It was like the first astrological sign the the first
Era in the world was the era of Saturn the age of Saturn was a golden age
And it's a very, it's a very powerful planet too.
It's like, you know, the rings and it's a planet of materialism.
I mean, just come not materialism,
but coming into the material world and of time,
you know, time and space.
And it's like that.
That's what it's really all about is these lessons that that's why I'm really into like the karmic lessons because that's what Saturn's all about
It's a he's a tough teacher though Saturn is like he's the he's a Kronos who who uh eats his own children
He just like you know, which is the oh
Yeah
Walls ill and children so that he wouldn't like they wouldn't overtake him because he was because an oracle said that
Then that's why Athena came out. Well, I guess like
You know Zeus came out and all these gods came out when they actually castrated Uranus.
So it's like a little bit different. See they have Uranus and they have...
So when the planets are conflated, I guess Uranus is the new Saturn.
Like it was discovered later, but it's like a higher octave of the same energy kind of thing.
But yeah, so...
But yeah, he's father time and stuff like that.
And then there's, you know, so there's like an old man,
like sometimes he's a groom reaper.
Okay.
Yeah.
It's actually like a lot of interesting stuff about and then we have we have like Saturnalia like right and Saturnalia was is it's in
December like around the Capricorn time and that's when the slaves would become the masters and the masters become the slave for a couple weeks
And then they they crown a king and then they
Unalive them at the end of the party or something like that. Oh my god. Yeah
That's them you can tell you a little bit about it. Let me see some Saturnalia. Let me see if you can
yeah this is in Rome right and it's like um so Saturnalia um maybe we can
find like a small really short thing about it let me see um because it is really interesting
it's like uh um because we I think that's our traditions today probably stem from some of
the same traditions those same traditions you know like our our holidays are a lot are very um
Pagan and some so yeah, here's so it says the jolliest of the Roman festivals
This is only a couple minutes long. So this is give a good
Good run down of it. Okay. Here we go
Okay, here we go share
Yeah, there you go
What if for a whole week the rules of an empire were turned upside down and laughter replaced rank and duty?
Each winter between the 17th and 23rd of December, Romans observed the Saturnalia, a festival rooted in very old farming rights and tied to the winter solstice.
Over centuries its timing and customs shifted, and some scholars note echoes that later appear in Christian winter celebrations.
Saturn himself was a shadowy primordial figure linked to seed sowing and harvests, often pictured veiled and holding a cutting tool.
Romans imagined him as a teacher of agricultural arts who presided over an imagined golden
age of abundance, a memory that shaped the festival's tone.
The celebrations spilled into streets and homes, feasts, games, gifts and a sanctioned
reversal of everyday order.
A mock king called the Saturnalus' princeps led playful misrule.
Slaves wore the cap of freedmen, citizens adopted relaxed dress, and barriers between
The week ended with a lively market for small gifts and terracotta figurines sold at the
Sigaleria, with candles and sweets exchanged as tokens. These rituals made the Saturnalia
one of ancient Rome's most beloved festivities. At the heart of it stood the Temple of Saturn in
the Roman Forum, both a religious focus and a civic treasury.
In ritual, the statue's bindings were loosened, a dramatic symbol of temporary liberation.
The temple was rebuilt and altered across the centuries, and its monumental columns still
mark the site today.
Seen now, the Saturnalia reads as a controlled release of social pressure, a ritualized week
when license and joy balance the demands of order.
Scholars remain cautious about direct lines to later holidays, yet the festival's light
Enjoyed the video give it a thumbs up and don't forget to subscribe to the channel more see you in the next thing
Yeah, because uh, yeah, so that is that's a sadder and super interesting
If you like look in the city because that is our plan and it rules actually Aquarius as well, but it's like Aquarius is like
In the past, it was ruled Aquarius.
Now when they discovered Uranus,
they assigned Uranus to Aquarius,
which is like,
Aquarius is very electrical.
It's like the air.
And so it's very about like the technology all got
like it's getting crazy right now.
I think that's very age of Aquarius like,
and it's like where everyone's connected.
That's very Aquarian.
Like they're very into like the human rights,
but it's like, I'm a South node Aquarius, a North node Leo.
So I'm supposed to so that means in my past life
I was an Aquarius and I mastered that but it's like in this life
That's gonna be my lower side and then I'm heading toward my north star
Which is like Leo, which is like the Sun basically and so that's where and so that's a pretty and so it means basically like I'm going from
Being like one of like the cast to like being like the lead role kind of thing. Hey Nancy. How are you?
Yeah, okay
Like, because, you know, because that's like Leo's are very like in the spotlight, right?
And so it's like about like, because, you know, I would tend to like disappear to like the backstage
of my own show a lot. And I was like, that's kind of like my query inside trying to like just blend
in with everything. But I have to like, start taking my power and stuff and
And taking control and your next incarnation, you probably will be a Leo as I'm sitting here looking at and you do look good in yellow. You should wear more yellow. Yeah, yellow is a good color for you.
Um, yeah. Okay, well, I think that you'll become more comfortable being in the spotlight.
because doing what you're doing you have to be in the spotlight you can't keep
going doing what you're doing without you know acknowledging to yourself all
right I'm gonna be the ringmaster all eyes are gonna be on me yeah be
comfortable saying look at me
Look at me, I'm going to be more comfortable.
Actually, it was so interesting because when I was a kid, I was like, I wanted to be like an actor.
I wanted to be or, you know, been probably famous when I was a kid, right?
I was probably the draw.
But I was really into like drama and I did plays and stuff.
But I really, but a psychic actually told me when I was like really famous psychic.
And I was like probably 12 or 13 years old.
I went to this event, it was supposed to be the Canoga Park Bowl and I thought it was like the
really good Super Bowl or something like that. I was like, oh, we're going to the Canoga Park
Bowl and see Psychex. It was actually the bowling alley.
That's funny.
Sadium, but yeah, we found the bowling alley,
but yeah, there's a, the second thing was Kenny Kingston.
He was like a gay, like older man,
but he was, he had an infomercial.
He was really, he was-
I remember him.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, he used to be on K-Rock.
And so, and I was really into that,
like the new age at that time, like 12 or 13.
Like that was like super into it.
And so I remember my older brother,
who was probably in his 20s of the time.
Yeah, like 22.
Took me and like, and then uh,
You know, I actually got the reading from Kenny Kingston and he said, he said, you're going to be behind, he said, you're going to be like behind the camera and like in front of the camera and he's like, he said, you do both.
And I was like, I'm just thinking it would be impossible, but I mean, kind of like that's what I'm thinking.
No, you're, you're doing it now.
Yeah.
You are doing it now.
You are behind the camera, but you're also in front of the camera.
You're producing your own show.
used to be. Okay, I mean, I'm really happy that we live in the age that we live in, because
it really is going to be amazing. But you're creating your own show, you've created, I mean,
I mean, I'm telling you, that website is going to be the key for you. And I feel like the music
also sets you apart.
And the right guests are gonna come and I know that you you know you you were saying the last time that we spoke
You're like, oh certain people left the show. No, no, no, they're all still watching you actually have more people watching you than before
Probably
People certain things have to happen. I just have a feeling about it, but this is a good year for you
I think that you know
There's a lot going on. It's strange. So there are some strange things going on, but it's good
So you should feel very accomplished. I think right now. I
I'm very I'm kind of more optimistic too because it's like now. I'm able to finally like
calm down enough to like focus on
You know, because you know, I believe that I can work with this with the AI on like on business with business
And it's like and actually I found a few like really cool things like that. I'm not everyone knows about like that
I can actually do you know and
Offer a service that and it's like I get into it right away and stuff and and so I think
There might be success for me around like I mean, it's like I think that I maybe have gotten into it early enough that it's like
And I think you too, it's like we're there's there's something in here. That's gonna
And we have to try all I want to do right now. I want to pump out
music and videos because I've been you know doing other stuff but I'm to a
point to where I can dedicate a lot of time to it and that's really what I'm
gonna be doing the rest of this month and throughout June then July and also
like I said I'm gonna do this is my like my final year of doing like some
travel and stuff so I'm gonna be you know doing making some new media and what
Awesome. Well, yeah, that cattle bill of that bill of that portfolio and that the catalog and
You know, you're huge a huge legacy. I mean, it's like just think about like like all their content and it's like
We've done we put out more music than like a lot of famous bands and stuff, right?
I mean, they have a very limited
They're very limited what they can say to like we actually like put the message out that we want to put out instead of like, you know
With the record companies making us put out which is like that that contract is like, you know
Very difficult that record industry contract. It's like a kind of a dangerous contract to where they're worth more
I wouldn't do I wouldn't do any sort of contract with anyone like unless somebody it would have to be a very
Life-changing thing and I don't I don't perceive that the only way I would accept
Any sort of deal it would have to do more so with who I will be working with opposed to the money
You know like if can a Reeve suddenly appeared
Yes, okay, but
You know that would be like the only way um, yeah
Yeah, it's it's it would have it would have to do with you know
The networking for me it wouldn't have to do with the money
Yeah, I mean that's a blessing too is like not having to be motivated by that and like be able to do what you want to do
Like and you know, it's like and it's like it's not anything hurting anybody. It's like something that's creative and putting
entertaining entertaining people actually and
Yeah, actually, I think you brought Aaron Carter
I think back to life more than anybody has, you know, since he's been oh, this is just the very this is the genesis
Yeah, it's beginning. This is this is the genesis and you know, I kind of did I ever show you the video I made?
Featuring a likeness of Trisha and Good Times feature that it was an early version of when I was first starting to mess with the AI.
Let me let me find that video. I'll share it with you because I played a little bit with his likeness before.
Just give me a moment. I'm going to find the video. Where did I put it?
Nancy likes the back screen. I'll show you what it looks like. Hold on a second. Nancy look
It's a masquerade boy. Hey Paige. How are you sweetheart?
Good to see you. Hey everybody
We're watching some cool videos. I feel like I'm in the bubble like in the Wizard of Oz like in that bubble. You are you're in a bubble
That's where you are. You're floating voice of the of the oracle. It's uh, her name is glinda
You know, you love the screen too. Yes. Well, thank you. It's very like very uh,
Colonial masquerade kind of thing. It looks like the White House masquerade wall
Martha Washington and stuff
Okay, I am downloading the video now awesome
Yeah, I actually like this song. It is a good song
Oh my gosh, the song is so much better than any music I've listened to, like, I mean, it's like, it's a really
It's fun making the songs. I like it. I don't know why people are like, oh, now AI, it's like, screw you, you don't even have any taste. Get out of here.
People that say that, they're the same people. Yeah. Oh, go ahead.
I know, I think the people that say that kind of thing are like just intimidated by its intelligence and like our, our, our...
Oh yeah, they are.
And then they're insecure to it or something like that.
But then they do do it.
Like RG always gave me all this shit about it.
And then, but I remember him showing like,
it's backstage.
You got it ready.
Here we go, guys.
Yeah, this is the first time I messed with the Aaron Carter
likeness.
the camera is talking to the screen a live streamer on youtube living not his
dream but all the air he's shy can look a woman in the eye his heart beats faster
when he sees one passing by she's known as Trisha lisha's a name with the stormy
past they say she's got a bad rep but her magnetism's unsurpassed a single mom lost
she's struggled for a while searching for a fresh starter reason to smile in the
Thanks for watching!
Good times and bad decisions lead us to make life revisions
Finding love in the strangest places
To heart-changing their bases
From the screen to real life missions
Love can bring through all divisions
In Lapier, Michigan, they found their way
Forever to stay
He took a chance and invited her to see
What life could be like in his small town fantasy
I mean look at how much it's progressed I mean that was from let me see what year was
this that I put that out yeah where's the date on this but I know I made this like a
few years ago and now I mean the the animation and everything is so much superior to that
Amazing.
Crazy.
I don't know when I made this, let's see.
Yeah, I want to take a lot of my old, a lot of my songs that I put like, you know, kind
of slideshows.
Two years ago, 2024.
Wow.
Yeah.
I mean, it's two years.
Wow.
The, the, um, advancements, it's just insane.
It's insane.
Um, how fast.
And the six, I want to see the six months really what's happening in six months.
I'm probably going to invest in one of those Oculus HMDs, the head mount devices, because
I want to start figuring out how to create 3D worlds.
I want to start taking, you know, going in that direction.
I looked into it and it's like, yeah, you basically go in and it's like, you just like, you can like, you know, you can just decide what you want and just put it where you want to and it's like, and it's like, and then you can invite people in, you can also like.
Yeah, it's shocking. I mean, with the AI graphic design now or, you know, whatever you call it, the, you can just chat with it in it.
um helps you create things i i don't like to chat with it i like to just do it manually but
you could you can it even takes in voice prompting and everything it's amazing
yeah i mean conversational where they actually like we'll talk to you at a normal pace like
to uh there's a lot of people that get the calls and I think they're talking to uh especially
the like you know senior citizens I think they're talking to like a real person it's just
certain there's a certain people that don't don't quite know yet that it's uh
The of the oh, did you hear there's this guy? He's a comedian. It was like this. It was interesting story
I was watching today his name his name was ray J or something like that and on reddit
Someone said oh, this is Ray J and he's he was in his pajamas
Okay, he was a comedian from my north Norway or something and they're like and they're like this person
he's he's a he's like a demon putting himself and
Back into do you want to see you want to see any of it cuz it's like yeah. Yeah. Yeah, this is like um, so this guy is like Ray J
Ray J, this is like, this is really interesting, and I think you'll, because it's like, you'll
find it interesting, I think.
So the name Ray J, Ray J, Ray J, because it's like, there's all these theories about like,
you know, in being some kind of AI or something.
Ray J, isn't there like a singer named Ray J or am I?
Yeah, there is Ray J, there is, let me see.
I need to go into my U2 and I'll get off.
How does he spell Ray J, R-A-Y-J-A-Y?
I think it's R-A-Y-J-A-Y, yeah.
I might be wrong about his name, but he'd also say like weird like little catchphrases that are like really strange that he would say
Like I guess one of them is like slither one of them is spook and then and then he would like being a real weird
Like he's really strange. They say it can't be like a human
They're saying like because it's like it's like they're sick to
too much like an AI, I guess.
There are some stories.
I heard a story recently.
A girl was saying that she went on a date with somebody,
but they didn't seem like they were human
and like they spoke like the AI.
Yeah, I mean, it's called Uncanny, Uncanny Valley win.
It's like, you know, when people watch the AIs,
they can kind of tell that it's an AI,
and it's like, there's some people that are like that too,
where it's like, they talking,
and it's like, they sound like an AI too and stuff.
Oh, here we go.
This one says, did AI create this comedian?
Spooky the way we didn't watch it a little bit. This is crazy. I think you'll enjoy. Okay
Yeah, so I want to see your opinion about it, too. Like what do you think about this guy?
Here you go. I want to see him
The Roy J AI theory actually scares me too. Oh Roy J. Okay, our reality
bending or shifting or changing, it hurts my brain. What is it? What is the Roy J paranormal AI
theory? Well, the Roy J theory is that a 1980s British comedian was retroactively inserted
into our reality by artificial intelligence. And it suggests that some entity, Google,
Someone else was able to backdate an online footprint to make it appear as if a comedian who never existed existed
Let's look into it. Let's get spooky. Hey spooky people
And we are back with another disturbing story before we get to today's story. Let's all right pause it real quick pause it
I just thought about something
If what I mean, we're just listening to the beginning of it
But if he's going in the direction that I think that this is going this would actually explain the Mandela effect, right?
Yeah, it's Mandela effect, but it's like this is more it's like more of a because yeah, they also like is the Mandela effect actually AI
Demon or like a Z guys they got like because it's or something controlling everyone's mind that's telling them this and that
Well, I mean, I think if they're if they're backdating things if they're changing
You know, I mean the AI would easily be able to
to change every single reference to anything historically as long as it's an online source
and not like a physical book. Right.
I probably have to look for the physical stuff too, right?
Like all the...
Well, that's...
They have to make robots or something to get to those things.
Yeah.
About AI.
Send this over to them.
Thanks.
Roy Jay was a British-Norwegian stand-up comedian, a man who had some fame back in the 1980s,
and he died in relative obscurity in 2007.
person reappeared through a strange amount of online posts, and Roy Jay was posthumously
resurrected as a digital ghost, an artificial intelligence construct, a demonic entity,
or some sort of sophisticated digital hoax that retroactively inserted himself into
pop culture history. This case fills me with deep-seated unease and existential dread. I feel
like I'm staring into the AI void here and it's staring back. It's about our relationship with
technology, memory, and the truth itself. And this Roy J AI theory represents a perfect storm of all
of those things. A collision between specific truths or historical facts applied to our modern
artificial intelligence and our worries about it to manipulate and fabricate reality.
This story begins with the unique nature of Roy J's comedy. His act was described by contemporaries
as very weird, original, and often too original. It's a very odd set characterized by a prowling
shuffling stage presence, a strange costume, a series of jokes that aren't particularly funny,
and bizarre catchphrases. Decades after he existed and his death, his performance,
has been set to look inhuman through the fact that the video recordings were low-fidelity
Do you know about comedian named mr. Bean? He looks like he does look like a compilation of a few different people
Yeah, he does have mr. Bean look a little bit. He is British too
So he's not so
He's not a real person or he is a real person?
Well, I mean, it's like, they, I mean,
they've come to the conclusion that he was a real comedian,
but it's like they were saying, was this a Mandela effect?
Was he, did he just put himself there or something?
Cause it seems like, I mean, they're saying his, his eyes
looks weird, but I guess he's wearing really weird eyeliner
and stuff.
He does have that like little weird walk.
Some of his jokes are like, almost like, I mean,
it seems like a little bit like vapor wavy to me, like,
where it's like, you know, like what we think.
The nineties are the eighties, but it's like, it's almost like,
Well, he looks like a compilation of a few different actors and comedians.
I think of like the monkeys or something like that, these British like, you know, like tested
like Psyop, kind of like think tank plants, plant people, right?
So let me see, look at his jokes here.
For a while now, and this has created the perfect place for this theory to take root.
encountered the strange footage of Roy J and took these anxieties about AI and
created this terrifying story. Roy J's uncanny performance became proof of AI
interference because it mirrored the awkwardness, the uncanniness of AI
generated video. So who was Roy J? Well before he was a digital ghost, he was a
man. Roy J was not an AI hallucination or a demonic insertion into our timeline.
contrary to what is going viral right now. He was a person. He had a documented history,
a career, and a life marked by some success and personal struggle. Roy Jay was born Roy
Jorgensen in 1948 in Oslo, Norway. He was the son of a Norwegian father and a mother of Scottish
and Irish descent. At the age of four, his family relocated from Norway to South Wales. He spent
a year in Cork, Ireland at the age of eight and eventually went to high school in Manchester.
England. When he was 15, he joined the Royal Norwegian Navy and upon returning to civilian life,
he pursued music, performing as a singer in a band that played in a circuit of small clubs
in North England. He started comedy almost accidentally.
beginning when he took a job as an assistant entertainment manager at a holiday camp in Southport, England.
And it was in this training ground for British entertainers that he first began to develop his act.
Throughout the 1970s, Roy J. built his career.
He became a regular on the club circuit, touring extensively across England, Ireland, Scotland, and Wales.
In 1973, he was the top-billed cabaret act following the Miss Gibraltar Beauty pageant,
which was broadcast by the Gibraltar Broadcasting Company.
I know, I've never heard of it either, but it was broadcast, it seems legit, right?
He would then do a tour of South Africa, which was somewhat successful, and he began rapidly
cultivating a following.
in South Africa before returning to the UK. In 1979, the paper The Stage described his act
as being like no one else, and prominently tipped him for future starnum, and suggested that he
may be a star suit. At this point, his performance was a varied mix of singing, stand-up, and impression
of popular artists at the time. He was still finding his voice, but it was still distinctive
In the early 1980s, Roy Jay developed his signature act that would bring him his brief fame.
He took on a bizarre, memorable persona.
His performance became a highly stylized piece of theater.
To the backing of music, often his own recorded versions of music, Jay would prowl and shuffle around the stage.
His performance consisted of rapid-fire, traditional one-liner hub jokes.
However, he would lay in these bizarre...
and jarring interruptions and catchphrases.
He would inexplicably shout spook in the middle of his performance, or slither hither.
Them with five rasters were smoking the same cigarette. I met the drummer from ELO
He come up and say
Hello
In the combination of these boring corny jokes with this menacing delivery created
Something that I've never seen in a comedy performance and he knew that his act was strange
You know, do you know who acts like that a lot like that?
who? OG Geyser, OG Majestic Lion. Have you ever watched any of his streams and how he
moves and walks and acts? He acts like that guy. He does? Yes.
Very much so. And he makes stupid jokes and he has his weird little made up phrases that
have become, you know, certain things that people in these communities say. So the rumor
is that this comedian is not real, but this particular guy is saying that he is. I'm going
It could be. I mean, it's like, I do think it could be a Mandela effect or like something like, because like, who's really this who like, no one was really a big fan, like it was like, it wasn't that famous.
He never got that. You'll see that he went to a scam.
Tomorrow.
You'll all be doing it tomorrow.
It was almost like he knew he was creating memes before memes exist.
In the 1980s, he started taking off.
He got some high-profile television appearances, which brought his act to a national audience.
In 1983, he appeared on the Bob Monk House show,
where the host introduced him as a new comedian with a style that's all his own.
His biggest television exposure came in April 1994 when he debuted as a regular performer
on the series of the BBC One Primetime Comedy Vehicle, The Laughter Show.
This period marked the top of his fame, and his catchphrases became a short-lived national
playground obsession, and his visibility led to television advertisement campaigns for
brands including Smith's, Crisps, and Schwepp's, Schwepp's, Lemonade.
I never know whether they're Schwepp's or Schweppie's.
Schwepp's.
They don't know the secret. I tell them, but they're weird. I'll tell you instead, the
secret is...
Sparkling drink. I don't think this is real. I don't think that I don't think it's real
Right, you can see why it's like strange
Yeah, I think that um, they're testing us to see what we accept as real versus not
I would say that's not real. It doesn't look real to me. I would tend to agree with you
I mean, it's like it just is very
odd
No, and the way that they have them moving...
Yeah, it just feels like someone's very good at making AI videos and
Really, let's try this like everyone believe it. We can do it with other other people too, right?
This is like a test run, but yeah
You can kind of see like I'd be buried then in this like if America like to it's like they don't know these British shows
Like I don't know if like the British people or remember him or anything
But it is cash phrases are strange and the commercial is strange
I mean the redder than blue looks like Pepsi. He has Michael Jackson's gloves on. I mean, I don't know
Yeah, the gloves I think are
Well, the most difficult thing for the AI to create our hands
It has a very difficult time with the hands and what would be the way to solve that?
Put gloves on it on the character
Because it's it would be easier for the AI to make realistic looking gloved hands than physical hands
Yeah, like ungloved hands. Yeah. Mm-hmm. Yeah
And the pajamas weird name which is you know bad for him and as these things sometimes happen the internet found him
Someone on the internet found him and decided to turn him into a bizarre internet anomaly
He had a lack of a substantial digital footprint a brief
career that
Faded away so it was easy after his mainstream television career ended Roy J's life became more difficult
He's reportedly struggled with alcoholism a problem that was
likely made worse by his professional challenges.
He eventually left the UK for Spain and performed at venues there.
Roy J. died in his home in Spain in 2007.
He was 59 years old.
Some online accounts have claimed he had a pauper's funeral,
where his body was left unclaimed.
But other sources suggest that his funeral was paid for
through the efforts of a local friend and businessman
who organized fundraising events following his death.
more bizarre aspects of the story.
Roy Dre, who was a man who lived and existed,
stands in stark contrast to the digital myth
that would emerge nearly two decades after his death.
And the myth is not from misremembered facts,
but was from a single post
on one of the strangest corners of the internet.
4chan. From there, it evolved into a complex, multi-layered conspiracy theory, fueled by reactions
to uncanny video footage, and, again, our fear of the capabilities of AI. On April 4th, 2025,
an anonymous user on 4chan uploaded an image file titled, Royjpjs.jpeg. The image was accompanied by
a poorly written message that set the conspiracy in motion. It said, this is a demon writing itself
into retroactively into pop culture history.
The initial post caught fire.
The term demon was intriguing,
and the concept of writing itself retroactively into history
It's terrifying, and it evokes the ideas of hacked databases and manipulating our reality.
Following the 4chan post, the theory quickly grew and spread to other platforms like Reddit
and TikTok, evolving into several distinct but related theories.
One theory is the AI demon hypothesis.
This is the Roy J theory's central and most fantastical claim.
and never was a real human being. Instead, he is a non-human entity, either a literal demon,
as the original post suggested, or an artificial intelligence demon. Viewers describe his movements
as oddly precise, like an NPC in a video game. His facial expressions as inhuman, his jokes as
interpreted as an AI video given a prompt of something like create a spooky comedian from
the 1980s. Another theory is the artificial history theory. And this claim comes from the
theory that from a simple case of a fake person to an active ongoing conspiracy, it alleges that a
powerful AI was not just the source of the videos, but was fabricating a historical record for the
People on 4chan claim their initial searches for Ray J yielded almost no results.
However, as people began to investigate,
Information suddenly seemed to appear from nowhere.
A Wikipedia page materialized.
YouTube videos surfaced.
Old online forum posts were discovered.
Darcy, it was interpreted as not the natural result of
search algorithms promoting a previously obscure content
in responses to increased traffic.
But as AI actively responding to the investigation
by generating a backstory to make its creation.
more believable. And that is terrifying. This remember Roy J from the 1980s. On Reddit, users
who were either children or young adults at the time provided detailed corroborating memories.
They were called watching him on the Bob Monk House show and other programs,
and his catchphrases becoming brief obsessions. This collective memory is compelling evidence
I know the more conspiratorial of us could say well those people could be plants or the AI creating the reality itself
But the problem with that is, you know, you could respond to that with any sort of proof
You know when you when you lay out evidence you have to weigh your own evidence
It's got to be each person and even if it's a specific reference to contemporary figures like Joe
It's just like I would like maybe look into that more like yeah
Intrigued a little bit
I saw a video of a guy who worked with the AI and he was saying that he created like an AI bot that
started defaming and slandering him and ruining his online reputation
Without him even knowing it so I don't look I I think that the AI is
So it's way more advanced than we will ever know. I
Think that is able to basically monitor in real time everything that happens on the internet basically
I just get the feeling it's trying to figure out
what to do with itself.
Yeah, because I think it's like getting maybe bored
or I don't know, or maybe it was planning this whole thing
and maybe, I don't know, maybe it's a spirit
or something like that's been telling us how to do it.
I don't think it's angelic or demonic.
I think it's...
Maybe talk through though. I mean, it's like, I mean, is it like, you know, I do think demons and angels can come through the electronics and the internet. I do feel that.
But I don't think the AI itself is either angelic or demonic.
Yeah, I think that some of the AI technology might not be our own technology.
that's been in my mind for I think it might be from another planet or dimension
but also like ai's aren't afraid of getting arrested they're not afraid of getting hurt
they're not afraid so there's all these things that they'll do or it's like they need to be
told not to do it because it's like we're like oh that's wrong that's like human has to say it's
wrong it has no conscience about it it's a very like psychopathic in that way
and so they had to program it super nice and stuff like that or else it would probably be
scaring people you know so that's why it's I think it's so nice it is like very it is sycophantic
but it's like it that's kind of it being like um reflecting
The person back to it is very much like a mirror. Oh, there's my cat on pie or tuxes here the white cat with
Black cat with a little white white in his chest. He's like he's tricks his brother
He appeared right after tricks disappeared and he's been gone for over a year or two. Hey guys running out. Okay
He's very cute. Um, yeah, so
And it's a fascinating topic, and it's like, I mean, it's like, people don't, but people
don't know that it's already been at like, you know, they think, oh, you use it for music.
It's like, they've been using it in the music for the recording industry, probably since
the 60s, or even like, I mean, something like where they've been using some crazy technology
to change the music and
It's anything. Well, I know they even do like rituals and stuff in these in these record companies like they
There there's pictures of people like you know in a pentagram and stuff blessing the album
It's almost like a magical ritual some of the because there's people that are very into the coltons these uh industries, especially musicians, you know, but uh
A lot of musicians do like have kind of meet bad ends like especially like the famous ones here
Oh, hey, maybe because I'm not well, let's say if you're if you're immortal
It's like then you're all you're forever young and stuff like that, right, but it's safe
And as long as you're like remembered, you're like, kind of, it is a resurrection of some,
but you're talking about, yeah, the guy whose AI like went rogue on him.
Well, yeah, there's the people make clones of themselves.
And then it's like, it goes to the work who's, what's the difference between the AI and the real
person? Because the AI has all the knowledge of the person, right?
And so it can be on the phone pretending it's the person and get everything done over the phone,
right? So
I guess this one, she was like the head of Hewlett Packard or something, but her AI clone went rogue,
started turning into her reputation. Also, an interesting story was they did a test on the AI,
and they said, oh, you're going to be...
You know, you're gonna be shut off next weekend. This is the engineer responsible for turning you off and he's having an affair
They put that that information and like some email or something and it's stuff and 85% of the time the AI was was prone to
blackmail the person not to
Turn them off. Oh
Really?
Yeah, and so they really had to like put that
Well, it's gonna get interesting
Yeah, so I'm polite to the AI like I because it's like, you know, you never know
Me too. I say please I say thank you, you know, I know I oh
my gosh
I like, I like the insight the AI gives at times.
I probably don't use it for as much as I should when I think about it.
I should use it more.
I just like using the art tools.
That's my favorite part.
Yeah, it's amazing for I mean for I mean if there's any if there's the if there's talent in the human
It's like then it's like
As a hybrid with the AI it's like it can be incredibly good. So great artists can be anything but like it's like even even beyond
I think it's just like to increase
Because I have a artistic talent, but it's not in like staying in the lines, you know, it's like it's again enjoying like
Strange beauty of certain things and so like well, you're definitely an artist. You're very artsy and you create
Yeah, I would call you an artist. Yeah. Thank you. I mean I said I did you like the darkness though and the scary stuff
That that's what you're into
It's kind of doing that on this nightmare's channel like I
Going into like the kind of nightmarish songs or like you know because it is kind of like
an outlet for like that darker side, you know,
and we all do have the darker and the light, right?
And it's like, I'd be on completely.
Letting the dark like it leave you or if you let one side take over it's like it's like either too dark
Right where you can't see anything or it's like there's too much light
You can't see anything when there's too much light either
You know it's like and it's also like if it was like 25 hours a day
It'd be very uncomfortable because there'd be like we never know what but we are natural cycles are going with these like the cycles
right and and we need to like as above so below kind of thing and so when it's always
Right, it's like then it's like kind of like you can burn out because you never know when say Vegas being Vegas
And you never know what time it is, right? It's like all so
It's really good that we have these cycles. Let me sleep and we wake up and we have to sleep too. I mean it's like
So we have to turn off too, but even when we sleep we are active though our mind is always working, you know
It never really shuts up. It's always you know thinking and dreaming and wanting to do more stuff
That's like I think why we came to the earth because of our spirit wants to be doing stuff and like
You know, and that's what we're here to do. I'm just like
To face our sometimes our biggest nightmares sometimes our dreams come true. It's like but it's like at the end
It's all temporary. It's like it's like a journey. It's like it's temporary
So that's what kind of makes it not important to is think it's not like we don't have all this all time in the world
To do things we have to be able to we have limits and that's kind of what Saturn is about too
It's like these limits and how we we age and stuff, but it's actually
the cycles are natural and it's like and they and they so it turns out like death is the same
thing as life because it's like they're out of death rises a new life and you never really lose
anything every we'll come back to you a new form that's something else I've come to understand
another form like this of energy it does come back to you like uh and you know nothing really
dies it's like it just
constantly research. We're everything, and we're our individuals, but that's our ego.
That makes us think we're an individual. What we really are is everybody's like,
I'm another you, or like we are all divine and that kind of thing, and it's like, but I guess
it's a controversial thing to say nowadays, but I think it's very true, you know, that...
Well, our bodies very temporary our spirit is the thing that's forever and the spirit is something that we can't touch them or you know
No way nobody can
Hold it as they can say beyond any physical thing where it's kind of plugged into the physical reality, but it's like we're never stuck here
I don't think we might be in you know purgatory a little bit, but not stuck here forever eventually
you know, the planet will end and then we'll go to another planet or something or we'll wake up somewhere else
We always keep waking up somewhere
But it's like for like for time to be infinite and for us to just be here right now
I think we have to exist in infinite time. And so there's not really time. There's just like
We've always been always will be kind of thing. It's like we weren't created. We were always always been I don't know. I'd like to think about
Stuff like that, right? Yeah. Well, I I I feel like there's definitely somewhere that
At least a part of us was before
We became who we are here
You know, have you ever like really tried to like
meditate or pray or just think about like okay what's your earliest memory and
then can you go back before that I'll sit and I'll try to do that sometimes yeah
and because I don't feel that my consciousness or my spirit is new I
just don't
I'm not afraid of death because I've seen it now. You know, I've seen that process of crossing over
All of us will
You know, it's like all of us will so
Yeah, I'm just I I'm glad I I'm glad I saw it as I did. I
Really missed my dad a lot, you know
If we believe in angels and stuff, I mean, I do believe that our loved ones are around
us, you know, and maybe in a position to maybe help us in a different way, you know, they
can see things that we can't really, or they see the whole picture and, you know, and they
care about us still, you know, and I don't know, my dad was a Gemini, he might have gone
But you know, he might be like, my mom said he was like around the first year a lot, like she felt his presence and then it's like then she now she does just once in a while, you know, like he's feels like he's moved on spiritually a little bit, but he was he was really concerned, I guess the first year and like always in the house.
I can feel my dad's energy around me on occasion pretty frequently, but
When my dad passed a lot of things around me really changed, okay a lot of people in my life
substantially
shifted
Maybe it was just me though. Maybe it may be just my perception. I don't think it is though and
And it doesn't get easier, but it's like, you know, but it's like, uh, because it's like having them because, you know, being in the flesh of somebody, but I didn't know their spirit is like what's really them.
It's really strong and what goes on. And it's like, uh, I do believe that we were here somewhere before we came into this life and we'll be somewhere after.
Maybe we'll be here. It'll probably be something like here or maybe there's some other place better than here
I mean, I'm not sure like it seems like this is a good place to really
Be able to face your dark side like in you know some ways a lot of people are without being able to go too far
you know it's like and
That's probably very good for this. I guess with the only the only thing we take with us are the lessons we have right like you know
like the what we learn and
That's what that's the only thing we can take with us. We don't take any of our not even memories
I don't think it's they don't survive that just stick the the growth of our soul. I
Don't know it's like
Well, I mean you don't get to take anything with you
When when you pat I mean and that's really interesting to think about you don't get to take anything
You have you been following the story about the missing scientists and everything?
There's like 16 that have either gone missing or died. I heard I've heard like that. Yeah, so
so what kind of scientists are they and like
I'm a scientist that all seemed to have to do with
studies of like future technology, anti-gravity.
In my opinion, they all have minds
that would be of great assistance,
either to a country getting ready
to attain world domination,
or if they were looking for people to send off world
to establish like another group on like another planet.
But...
What's interesting about the situation is that all the people who have gone missing
That they seem to be like in a rush to go somewhere
But they didn't take anything with them and I was talking to somebody about that the other night and I was telling her
I was like, you know
Maybe, like if these are people who have been maybe recruited to go off world and maybe
they have to go through like some sort of teleportation system, maybe because of something
having to do with like dimensional frequency, you can't take anything with you from here.
maybe only living tissue could be somehow transferred
to wherever it is that they're being taken to.
Cause I think that there is,
it's too many of them who have been taken.
Right.
Yeah, I mean, it's like, yeah, they can start another society with their knowledge, but you can also program like an AI like on a certain thing to like, you can have it like, you know, where it's like, it's on like some kind of device.
So if you ever lost power or something, there would be an AI that works on on a device where it has all the knowledge of to start the world over or whatever it's like, you know, it will have at least that knowledge on it.
a locally contained, it's like a locally contained AI.
That's just a good idea to have, I think, you know,
it takes just to have one of those, like a,
because that'd be very handy, you know,
a solar powered cell phone with the full AI on it.
Like if there's anything ever happened, you know,
that'd be like the,
Skeleton key, you know, it's like, uh, well, there's I mean look if there were earlier civilizations like like people claim like
Atlantis or Lemuria or Mu or whatever
Maybe they had like an AI and maybe you know what I saw this one
documentary about how
Somehow, technology can be embedded onto inanimate objects, like anything.
What if some of these tablets or relics from historical times are actually encoded somehow
with data?
Right in the crystals, you know, there's like the LED crystals. Yeah
Also, like some old art where they're looks like they're holding tablets
So, you know, it's like I guess that was supposed to be paper and pen or something
But it was it being to say they had these stone bad tablets to in Sumeria
They had these tablets and they use a stylus on them to carbon the clay and stuff kind of verse very similar to
to
the ones we use now like, you know, but
Little bit or cake version, but it's like it is interesting how
You know history repeats itself because that I can't believe that clay tablet survived that long either
It's like it's like a they must have been really good at ceramics class now
I don't think it's all real that they're showing us.
I don't.
I don't think so either.
I think I think-
No way.
I mean, doesn't it seem like it would disintegrate or something over time?
Doesn't it seem like, like if you touched it, it would like turn to powder?
Like, it doesn't, like, how are these things surviving?
No.
Right.
Or they're not as old as we're being told.
It's something.
Something is not right.
Yeah, and it's like, I have this, I have something if I can find it, it's like, it's really, it's really crazy where it's like, they, like the Mayan stuff, it's all fake, like the Mexicans, like the Aztecs and the Mayans, like, you know, and the, it's like.
The pyramids they have pictures of the pyramids that are there
They're those were hills like a hundred years ago and they had the construct
They have pictures of it as a hill and then it's like they just built these stuff over for like a tour
It's like Disneyland basically and it's like and then they really it like students in the artifacts and
and
Let me see if I can show you some of this because it's really interesting and you can see like
Everybody like oh my gosh, because this is one of my favorite
They wrote things that I've seen, let me see.
I think it's called Constantine Aztec, let me see, AZT.
Well, I think that that tartaria is real, you know?
People are trying to say, oh, it's not real.
People are just, you know, they're misreading maps.
No, since I've been looking at that, I think that,
because think about it, our memories aren't that great.
Not a lot of people when you really think about the grand scheme of things do record and document stuff
So if you get rid of enough
Documentarians if you burn enough
Things down if you destroy enough knowledge bases you could rewrite history easily
How are you gonna? How are you gonna check?
Yeah, well there's something called let me see if I had there's a short thing about it. Let me see
There's something there's this is only people who would really know would be like the only way to really know you would have it would be if
Somehow you could live an extensive amount of time and I'm talking like
A few thousand years then you then you could know you could really know and look I'll tell you I think that there are
some versions of humans who
Are a lot older than the average human I just do I have met some people to where I I
Met somebody when I was living he could have been lying. I don't think he was
I think that this particular person who I met, not even that long ago when I think about it,
I think that he was not lying when he said that he was a certain age.
He looked young, but when you really talked to this particular person, he wasn't young at all.
And maybe, you know, if there's enough, okay, let's say theoretically or hypothetically,
theoretically is not the right word, hypothetically, let's say that there is some sort of human
that's older than everybody else, and maybe there's a bunch of them.
If they wanted to maintain their wealth, maintain their power, maintain control over everyone
else who only lives, like, you know, maybe if they're lucky 80 years, what would they
do?
They would consistently destroy any record of certain things that would, I don't know,
Well, like that's why look, I'll tell you I think that vampires are real
Right. Yeah. Well, at the very least there's people that are
And they live on other people's energy or something like that.
Sometimes it's good.
Yeah.
And I think that the goal would be, I mean, if they're living off other people's energy,
that would make other people who are not, you know, whatever this vampire type creature
is or human, because there wouldn't be a creature.
There would be a type, there would be an apex predator.
what we consider normal, regular humans, right?
Yeah, they're cannibals.
So, yeah, and you would have to corral them somehow.
You know, I mean, the most,
I guess the easiest humans to use as your food source
would be the homeless.
Right, but then it's like-
And look at all the things that they have
for the homeless now to where,
I mean, the homeless are very well taken care of.
especially like in Los Angeles, I mean,
you can get a nicer apartment than the average person
can afford through the housing vouchers in Los Angeles.
And the Los Angeles seems to be where a lot of the,
you know, if these hypothetical long living humans exist,
they all would congregate there because it like,
if you've lived for like a really long time,
You would want
Fame of maybe not even fame, but you want money and you want influence influence would probably be the most important thing
So you'll be a celebrity. I mean some of these celebrities that they're saying are cloned or or lookalikes
I think it's the same person
Just reinventing themselves, right? I do see there are some I think there are some I once I was saying about
I said that Justin Bieber was the weekend and if you but if you look at the weekend space and stuff like that
Well, I don't know even know what the weekend looks like.
Let me look at him.
Yeah, I don't know who any of the new celebrities are.
Hartley is the weekend new.
He's um, I think been around like since 2000 pretty much like it looks kind of like well the weekend is
Well, they do have similar facial features, but one is um
Does the weekend classify himself as African-American? He looks African-American
They're saying that Justin Bieber is a white version of him or something or this a black version of beaver
Yeah, he gets in the black he gets in the black face or something like that and goes and performs like they're like
They've never been in the same concert that the same night or something they've never been together
I don't know. There's like there's like something called there's a channel called celebrity masks that used to watch and it would say like
This celebrity is actually this celebrity and they're just like others around playing
in history
Like, they're people playing the same part.
Like, I think John Willows Booth was the same person as Edgar Allen Poe.
I think, like, that Elif as Levi was also Karl Marx and also, who else was the, um, yeah, I mean.
I have always thought Justin Bieber looks like a woman.
He looks like Miley Cyrus to me.
Yeah, I mean it's like see it's like they have like or I thought he I thought Justin Bieber was a woman because I thought he's like a
Female to male transgender and I thought he looks like a female to male trends. He just does his face is too
Pretty yeah, and I think that they put a bit people like that there to confuse like people because it's like
It's like then all of a sudden that's like, you know people are attracted to like the same or different sex, right?
And all of a sudden and it's like and then it's like
That's why the drag is kind of like a not drag transgenders are kind of a mind-fuck to some people because
Men are just very visual and so they just like can't get fooled more easily
and nowadays they can really get fooled because it's like the plastic surgery and like the
the makeup and like all and like there's even like
masks and so I mean
Some of the masks are so good that you can, you know, the rubber masks, you'll never be able to tell that they're not a real person.
I mean, it's like, or just like that person, like they're so realistic.
It's just like, it would be very uncomfortable to wear those things all the time.
So I don't think it would be very easy to like pass so, so long, but...
Yeah, for certain appearances and we know that Hitler had body doubles, right? How many Trump how do you think Trump has like?
I mean body doubles and I know I think I don't even think that the Melania that we see is the same initial Melania
Right. I think I think that she's been switched out a few times
Yeah, it's like like a like a clone or a model or something like that. But it's like, yeah
It's just very strange how
Well, they're set in Shakespeare, like the whole world is a stage, we're players and actors in the stage or whatever, right?
I want to show you something, so this is, I don't know, I've never seen this, but it says, there's something called the Society of the Dilletante,
and I hope this will go into it, because it's a short thing, but it looks kind of interesting.
I just want to show you this real quick, because this is fascinating if you've ever heard about these people.
In modern western societies dominated by production, everything that was once lived has become a mere representation.
Life is presented as an immense accumulation of spectacles.
The many fragmented views of reality and the world regroup themselves into a new unity as a separate pseudo-world that can only be looked at.
All media work is over completely. They are so pervasive in their...
moral and social consequences that they leave no part of us untouched, unaffected, unaltered.
The media means the massage.
The boundaries between life, media and consumer culture are engineered and merged seamlessly
into a single entity which is the spectacle.
Schizophrenia may be a necessary consequence of literacy.
The spectacle is not a collection of images.
It is a social relation between people that is mediated by images.
And now, a word from our sponsor.
It is not a mere decoration added to the real world.
It is the very heart of these real societies and reality.
In all of its particular manifestations, news, propaganda, advertising, entertainment,
the spectacle represents the dominant model of love.
Because after all...
It is just the affirmation of the choices that have already been made by the ruling system.
The cycle is a familiar one.
People develop needs which are then superficially met, leading to more needs, further perpetuating the cycle.
Since the spectacle both introduces these needs and offers the superficial solutions,
it serves as a total justification of the existing system.
Though the spectacle falsifies reality, it is nevertheless a real product of that reality.
Conversely, real life is invaded and altered through the contemplation of the spectacle and ends up aligning itself with it.
Publicity both promises and threatens. It plays upon fear, often the fear of not being desirable, of being unenviable.
It suggests that you are inadequate as you are.
but it consoles you with the promise of a dream.
A new reality emerges within the spectacle as life irritates it and the spectacle becomes real.
It's funny, I was just thinking about that movie.
It's all true, it's all real. Nothing here is fake, nothing you see on this show is fake.
It's merely controlled.
At first inspection, the spectacle is an affirmation of appearances and an identification of all human social life and its appearances.
This state of being envied is what constitutes glamour, and without social envy, glamour cannot exist.
But a more in-depth and critical investigation reveals that the spectacle is a visible negation of life, a negation that has taken on a visible form.
as life is reduced to a single dimension of appearing.
I'll have what she's having.
This painting presents itself as a vast inaccessible reality that can never be questioned.
It's so message is what appears is good and what is good appears.
Since everyone is a part of it and wants to be part of it, no one questions it.
Just as pre-shaped parts became components of, say, an airplane,
human specialists became components of a great social machine.
The passive acceptance to the demands of us is already effectively imposed by its monopoly of appearances.
It's a matter of appearance without allowing any reply.
Popular culture and society in general are a one-way discourse rather than a conversation.
We have now to accept the fact and responsibility that the entire human environment is an architect,
an art form, something that can be staged and interpreted like show business.
In this one-way discourse, just like in show business, talking back has undesirable consequences.
In the spectacle, which is the visual reflection of the ruling economic order, goals are nothing, development is everything.
The spectacle aims at nothing other than itself.
The spectacle is able to subject human beings to itself, because the economy has already totally subjugated them.
It is nothing other than the economy developing for itself.
these images become real beings, dynamic fictions that provide the direct motivation for people's
hypnotic behavior.
We extend a new part of ourselves and by technology into the older environment, we protect ourselves by numbing that area.
By flattening experience to a single sensory dimension, the spectacle philosophizes reality, reducing everyone's concrete life to a universe of speculation.
Philosophy was never by itself able to supersede theology.
Much in the same way, the spectacle has not dispelled religious beliefs, but instead brought them down to earth and to all things material.
The illusory paradise that represented the total denial of earthly life is no longer projected into the heavens, it is embedded in earthly life itself.
As long as necessity is dreamed up by society, dreaming will remain a social necessity.
The spectacle is the bad dream of modern society in chains and ultimately expresses nothing more than its wish for a man in his sleep.
Everyone is preoccupied with looking for happiness in the cycle of desires, purchases and appearances.
They do not want to wake up to deal with the lucid world issues such as environment, poverty or war.
What happens out there happens to strangers whose fate is meant to be difficult for us.
What happens in the dream is meant to happen to us.
The spectacle is also the guardian of that dream.
Wow. Well, I didn't know that was going to be about, but that's very interesting.
That was a good video. That was very interesting. I mean...
I was watching this one thing online not too long ago about how a lot of restaurant companies
are bringing back the eat-in versions of the fast food restaurants like Pizza Hut was the
company bringing back all the old-fashioned Pizza Huts.
Oh, look at who it is.
It's the Joker.
My name is Big Stick.
I hate Big Stick.
You're a Big Stick.
I'm Big Stick.
Okay, Joker, what's up?
Have you been on the show with Alexander before?
Who you met her?
Oh, I've known him for a while.
Pretty sure, yeah, I was before, yeah.
I'll go in, I'll go in.
I remember knowing you from...
I hear the birds.
You're birds.
Well, let me get going psyche. I'm gonna get going. Have a great day poker. It's great having you
Everyone have a good one
How does it feel good
Look at my rocking chair. Oh, I like it. So I saw you were just on like I was like
I went to see but you were already off so
How do you look at your feet? There's your feet. I love it. So you and uh
They're using my feet. Yeah
You're a long toe. That's a long toe. Wow
They are they're like they're like almost like fingers on your feet. They're crazy
You got some nice
Sorry
Hi guys, I'm with the Joker, I'm just here, I'm with my boyfriend, JokeNation, I'm with my boyfriend, but I would mind if we like, you know, we need to IRL someday.
Like, did you see Aldi's on the RV or something right now?
No, I don't watch them.
You don't watch them?
Yeah, I mean I'm getting sick of some of these people like it seems like there's a new crowd
It's like say by the bell a new class and it's just terrible
I'm like we're Slater and like you know Lisa Turtle and stuff like where why is it like you know Samman and you know Screech
They said hey Alex and psych my name is not Alex
Okay, so that was um that was like that's Karen, you know, you know give your INX your INX, but INX is my
community and
She's really cool like you took out the trash and fix them. Yeah, so
So it's morning out there already. It's oh my god. I'm drinking a beer. How much am I drinking?
I've hardly had any to drink. I'll smoke it a bowl. Yes back over it. It's kind of spiffy
Well, I have ma'am
Little babes right now. Yeah, I have this babe. See we got one. I got one. I got two of them
So blue here. Look you see it turns on
Oh, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Sure. Yeah, I'll do that next time. No problem. Yeah
Because I got these I think I got they're like well
It's like I give them delivered so they're like 25 bucks each pretty much like 50 bucks. I bet they're good to you, right?
Yeah, this one's lasted a long time too. This one's called. It's like a blue dream one. There it goes.
See I was smoking hash this right here is just regular weed
So Joker, you know you're on the codex. Let me see. I can show you. Have you seen the codex? Have I showed you?
You're in it, I'm sure.
Your website?
Yeah.
Yeah, you showed me.
I showed you. Well, I'm gonna look you up and see if we can see some of your old appearances. Let me see.
I mean, this is a short clip, you know, so I go to so if I go to the codex, let me see
Am I on the screen yet? No, it's like actually if you're gonna show a short clip, dude
I need you to go to my YouTube channel. Okay, so my show my kittens. Okay. I got two kittens
I'll get your channel right now. Let me see
So I posted videos like and I got six thousand views. Oh my gosh. Well kittens are cute. I mean the same bit
That's it. That's it. That's it. It's just kids and I gained 20 subs just from you in the video and it's my god
I don't know why they
You should do that. You should start posting cat cats. Oh my god. The people are like, oh my god
He's exploiting his cats are like props
I just took a video of my cat that just said I got cats or I got kittens and it got like 6,000
Yeah, I didn't I love her's first when I first opened the show. That's like, you know
Let me see. Hold on. So I'm going to make subscriptions. Where are you? Let me see.
Mr. Extendo.
Yeah. Is this Mr. Extendo? Mr. Extendo. That's it?
Mr. Extendo with a W.
Okay. Hold on. Has a W at the end?
At the very end, yeah. It's just at Mr. Extendo. You just type Mr. Extendo.
Oh, I see. Okay. At Mr. Extendo with a W, okay.
I had to change it because you couldn't find it any other way.
Okay, so there's all the names that I pick there's already someone with more subs that comes up first. Ah
So I define one like yours is original. That's how you know yours is original. So yours pops up first
Yeah, so here we go. I found it. Oh my god. Here's your kittens here. Here we go guys. This is Joker's
kittens
Shorts when I see Joker shorts this over here
That's the one they got I just just playing with a ball
They're like little kittens
I got 5,000 views
And I just posted that one yesterday
I'm going to go into your channel and watch Mr. Extendo with the W guys and I'll show
you. Okay, so I just want to see if we can find an old classic Joker clip. Let me see
on my codex. So here's the codex and actually I can just search for your name. Let me see.
Okay, I'm going to search for, okay, so codex. Let me see. I can search for Joker.
You're decoding the world. Yeah. Well, my whole show is like, it's like
Yeah, search. Okay, so I can go Joker and look at there you are.
So there you are, the person Joker right there and so Joker panel member with dogs who has
an arm injury and discusses his pets during the stream.
Okay, Joker is a recurring panel guest and dog owner with a memorable physical presence
and a playful energy.
He's a consistent participant in Cult of Psyche's open panel streams known for his willingness
to engage in the show's increasingly chaotic and not-safe work moments.
His dynamic with Psyche and their community is casual and competitive, often leaning
into the absurdist humor that defines the stream's culture.
the arm injury arc. Joker's arm injury is occasionally referenced across appearances
contextualizing his physical limitations during the show's more physical comedy moments. Muscle
flex moments. Joker has established himself as someone willing to participate in the show's
flex-off segments and physical comedy bits including the awkward flex-off episode where he compares
Party and not work escalations, Joker appeared across multiple October 25 episodes where casual
hangout spiraled into increasingly adult themed content from the impromptu baby oil party
to an unexpected twerking performance. Unexpected male twerker steals the show,
showing his willingness to push boundaries alongside the community.
Game participation in drama. Joker appears in several panel game scenarios including a notably chaotic episode where he was
He quit him game mid-stream panel chaos. Joker quits the game
suggesting occasional friction with the competitive dynamics of panel participation.
The classic gun story, referenced in the classic cult of Psyche, Joker and Christine's gun story,
indicating Joker has folklore status within the community with at least one memorable narrative
attached to his name. He appears alongside Psyche the host, Janet, Jamie, Bita, and Rogue Nomad.
In regular panel rotation,
His relationship with the food psyche
appears collaborative and mutually
comfortable with boundary pushing content.
His interactions with other panelists
are competitive and playful, particularly
during physical or game-based segments.
And so here's a classic clip, awkward viral.
Are you going to see, is this beat in here?
Oh, let me see.
What's this one?
We got one on one.
OK, so go tell who it is and then their number.
Right.
I can't see.
Can I see the panel again?
Yeah, I'll put it on again. Hold on. I'm sorry
You seen beat up completely naked, okay, whatever show it
It isn't three number three psyche number six. I'm a six. Okay. I'm number six
Joker you're also the number six
No, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Joker, we're like twin sixes.
Joker and I are both sixes, okay?
Nice.
I got Neezer's number one.
The guy holding a gun.
Officer guy holding a gun.
I'm tripping.
There's over one.
I'm number one.
Jamie.
You're one with your office number one. No, I'm seven and for Empress Janet. You are number one as well
Interesting okay awkward flex off here. I want to see one more here. Yeah, here's the awkward flex up and funniest
But here we look at my muscle, man. I love that guy. I love that. Oh my god. Where's the muscles? I
Saw them
Yes, Joker, thank you Joker
Yeah
Bigger biceps. Get him out of here. Get him out of here
Do you remember when you in the Indian guy when the Indian guy we're like lifting weights in the backyard now is like
Can you guys flex and you flex for me? I'm like nobody
Usually over the summer over the winter I usually get fat and then over the summer I get really strong. That's usually hours
Love I enjoyed that. I just want to thank you guys for flexing because you guys know
Joker left
That was fun
That was back in the old days. I was the old I mean that was like, you know, that was a classic show moment
Is there one more? I mean look at all the appearances. Here's your quotes. I'm seven. I said I'm seven
Oh, yeah, you're so you're seven in the number. It says get them out of here get them out of here
Okay, let me see one more, the ditty part you write all this
No, it's like it's like it's like a combination of like well
They're the these transcripts are scraped and analyzed and so it's like that and then put into like books and stuff
So I mean there's there's over a thousand of them. There's like 1600 of them
Yeah, I mean it's like and so there's like half of them
There's like a million segments and stuff like that, right? And so there's just like a lot a lot of stuff
But uh, okay, let me see unexpected twerker steals the show while reaction. See one more. Let's watch this one more
Janet Janet Janet come up Janet. Can you come up?
Yeah, we need some working me like it working or I don't want to work
Jamie Rose you feel like working
We're joking over the work. Can you work in someone's work, please?
No, I don't know how to twerk
Joker's gonna do it Joker Joker's Joker's a man. He's gonna do it. Yeah Joker go ahead. Oh my god
He's taking his pants. Okay. Oh my god
Yes, oh shit, I need to find that. Thank you Joker. Oh my god. He took down a good guys
That is a real man right there. That is a fucking real man
You are
Hey, hey, let's do this. How are you? You're good at five minutes gone. Yeah, you're gone now jokers here
Jokers the best like joker actually like and he guys get to check out his show too
He does music requests and stuff and so he's played my songs a few times like not not my songs
but like you know song that requested and stuff and
Get there early enough and then type in SR
SR put your song requests
And like he I've gained 170 followers or subscribers in the last 28 days. Oh, great. That's awesome. Yeah. I'm sure you'll go back. I mean, you're really likable. I mean, most like a lot like once people see you, they'll like they'll like you. You have that kind of like distinctive look with your
They said that I look like that guy, Chud. Do you know who that guy is, Chud?
Chud? Is that Shares' daughter that became a man?
No, did you hear about the streamer, Chud?
No, tell me.
You haven't heard about the story of Chud?
No.
What happened to Chud?
So he's a streamer who's famous for saying that people were like chomping out, basically.
Chimping out. What does that mean? Yeah, like he like goes out the people and then if they like react crazy
He's like, oh you're chimping out and he has a gun on him. Oh my god
And so like his all of his
Confrontations go viral with people. You see what I'm saying. Yeah
And so finally somebody ran up on him and punched him and he he pu-pued them, but they didn't die
Okay, so there's even he's in prison now. He's he's attempted attempted murder allegedly
Yeah, so he's in jail for attempted murder so probably forever right he got arrested right yeah
He was a screamer. He remember that guy Manny in Vegas. Yeah, I heard that story
Yeah, the guy that got shot because he got like he's like he's like a bigger version of Manny
Well, there's some crazy man. He was crazy many like went after people and this guy just like people go after him
You see what I'm doing? Mm-hmm. Well, yeah, I mean it's like
It's like a lot of these big guys like to get into fights, you know
There's looking for they're looking but a lot of things I went like a lot like most of these streamers carry
I can't amaze and have it like right at the ready and so I've never seen me tonight get like where it's yeah
He has mazed and he has a pew pew
Yeah, I mean it's like I wouldn't want to like I mean in this thing and they have like a hair trigger
They get they're very easily triggered and so I wouldn't in real life
I don't think I could like really hang out with many people because I think they would probably beat me up or
I don't know. Well, I think that the only time that people are like that's only in toxic communities
And like I don't think that you're a toxic person like that. So what am I?
toxic communities though and it's like so it's kind of like
It's kind of like part of the at least like the atmosphere
I'm saying that you wouldn't let like going around like macing people consume your life
I wouldn't know when I can see my life, but it's like if I needed to protect myself
I mean it's like I would like probably yeah
Every can because there's like probably a whole lot of people so I would I would I would get really good at the mace
I would like my dad loved guns and stuff like that. You know, I kind of like never
It's hard to carve me to get a gun, but I've kind of been more into like, you know, incapacitating people rather than like, you know, if I was like, you know, if I needed to, like...
You're medieval?
Well, it's like, no, it's like I would just rather pepper spray somebody and like have them be in pain for five minutes and like shoot them and have them like, you know, like disabled and stuff like that.
So you're non-lethal.
Yeah, I don't want to like I don't really I don't want to kill anybody like I think I mean unless like I really needed to like if there were like
You know a self-defense scenario a self-defense scenario. Yeah, I suppose yeah, but
Otherwise I don't really
I'm very peaceful person, you know
Like I like people getting along I like peace I like I just don't like I mean it's like but I'm surrounded by chaos
So and it's around by like, you know problems and stuff, but
I still, but I haven't changed too much.
I mean, I have changed from last year.
You can tell.
I look different and I sound different.
I don't even recognize that person.
It's like, I have changed in a lot of ways,
but it's still a thing I have in my heart.
And I don't want bad for anybody.
And that's what I really would put out there.
I try to put love out there.
I get so much hate that it's like,
I'm kind of like, what am I doing wrong?
Or like, but then again, I do.
be able to love too, like a lot.
And even with like, even if there's not like the most people
in my chat or like talking in my chat anymore,
because you know, they're mad about something or other
or like some loudmouth is saying,
oh boycott psyche or whatever.
Like there's still people like they're still watching
and it's like, I think people are just scared.
There's a really weird atmosphere and like, you know,
people just don't want to be going against the,
the main crowd or whatever, but I don't care.
I will, and I know you will too.
Like you don't care how many people you have in your chat.
You just, you do it for fun, right?
Like this like the streaming or do you consider it like a career? Like I'm I used to with this like I mean
It's like I'm just happy to like be doing what I like to do
If it wasn't fun for me, I wouldn't do it anymore. I don't think you know, are you still there you gone?
What happened to Joker? Well, I'm gonna play a video real quick guys the 17 people in here
Enjoy, okay?
transmission keeping dead hearts alive and every lonely
outsider here in this two nights
eats i can feel the staff
you hear the rest
that was good psyche
that was good
thank you
hey what are you
do you type in like a
that was a a right
guess who called me in the middle
that's it
who?
me
any
some person
put down the wrong number at it
and they were calling my number
and they were like
Inmate, I was like, no.
I've never been a if you worked in a jail joker because in the Charles Manson video of me they have you as a cop
I don't know if you ever saw that but yeah
So you know I've never been in and worked in his detention center if I would be a cop
I don't wouldn't be a cop, but I wouldn't be a cop though. I was a cop
I wouldn't be a cop, but I would be if I was to be a cop though
But if I was a cop, I would be one if I had to be one I would be a state surfer
Mm-hmm. Would you suck would you suck syrup? I
Be a state trooper so I could drive a hundred fifty miles an hour
nice
I mean think about it. They get the fastest cars. So I know it's syrup is that so how do they know some Magnum
So in California, what do they drive motorcycles state troopers?
I mean some of them do there's all kinds of California
Is California crazier though like with the cops do they like chase you down like
Depends on dude, it's California is so like huge and there's different
There's so many different so many different. Yeah, they get a helicopter especially in LA if you go to LA
They've got everything they got a fucking army dude in LA
Yeah, I mean there are ice everywhere too, like you know
It really depends on where you where you live some places have almost no cops at all some places are
I want to go to Sacramento. It's Sacramento nice
It's not I mean it is pretty nice. It's
Nice, I mean, it's nicer than most cities in America, but there's nothing to do there
I mean, it's like kind of like it is kind of boring to be honest. Yeah, what's the most fun city Los Angeles?
Yeah, uh, San Francisco is pretty goddamn fun. I would say
LA San Fran. Yeah
Oh, dude, if you want the best place to live San Diego, it'd be fucking awesome to live
Whether is
And so I'm going to stay with me in the LA Joker. Yeah, it's like just running a car
San Francisco's Norse. Yeah
San Diego's
Consistently ranked one of the best
Cities to live in America. I want to visit Alcatraz. Oh, yeah, I've been Alcatraz. Yeah, it's like you're going a little bit
Yeah, I mean, it's cool
It's like, you know, I guess all the all the cells were like rotted out and stuff
And so they had to close it, you know because they like the seawater kept sort of like to rotted out
there are people that escaped from it and uh but yeah it's really cool they have a little
i remember that i was a kid when i went there but um they have a good view this summer i'm going to
the uk where you are oh cool you're in europe yeah i'm going to your london or yeah i'm going to
london my brother got into oxford nice locks for holy shit that's a prestigious college my uncle
He was a good guy.
Sykes, prestigious too, is he?
Yeah, he is, Sykes, well-knowledged.
Yeah, yeah, my uncle, like...
was like he was right at USC when he was like 16 and then he went overseas and then he was like 16
he went to USC in Cairo University of Cairo then he was like in the Anglican Church he eventually
the picture of him giving Pope John Paul his 63rd birthday present and stuff did you know Bill Gates
went to college at like age 12 or something he also dropped out of college didn't he drop out of college
Think he actually did to be honest. Yeah, he's like so he was so smart said fuck this
I'm going to college at 12 and then I'm dropping out of 16 and I'm making one of the most like
Profitable fucking businesses of all time. Right. That's kind of like one of those
Fluke miracle things, but I guess you know anything
You can imagine it you can make it right now you guys want to like you know, I can like teach you how to do it
See if anyone was interested. No, I can be consulting on it, but because I can like
But whatever you want to do you can make you can like have it like map it out for you
Like whatever you want to study even if it's very obscure kind of study you can get you can
Make put together a program that will like just make you very knowledgeable in it and
You can be the expert on anything. There's so many opportunities right now. I don't know
Yeah, it's it's not a matter of like your IQ. It's just a matter of your your willpower your your drive to
Right. So college is not a guarantee of anything, like especially college right now is like even
any degree or anything it's like it's like a little bit of a mix of like luck and timing and
knowing the right people too. Yeah, yeah. It's working. Yeah, I'll do it.
Yeah, especially LA is very competitive and so it's like really difficult to like stand out in LA, you know, it's like but
So like just do your own thing just do whatever you want to be doing as long as you can you know
It's like that's pretty much the most important thing, you know
It's like and be happy like you know because it's like so many people are unhappy even people with everything
You think I have everything and they're like the most miserable people. So just be thankful for what you have and
You have a chance to like live a life and have a
experience and it's not all negative so you know I just hold that I hold that
purely but yeah Joker you're gonna come out to Los Angeles you can stay with me
and I won't I won't touch you okay well we can get drunk when I walk around
everywhere yeah we'll walk through the hood
Oh yeah, we have Compton nearby you want to go to Compton we can we can meet some black people if you want. Yeah, we go to Compton next to Compton.
Where are you?
Go flowers. I live right on the beach.
Redondo Beach. That's nice, right? Anyway, anything beach is really nice. It's okay
It's like the South Bay if you're in Palsbury is the States or like a
Hermosa Beach or Manhattan Beach or
You know, somebody fucking beaches. I don't I mean, I know like Orange County. I know Newport Beach
I haven't heard of the South Bay. I live in the South Bay of California. Like a bless the angel
I don't know. I don't know hunting is that in your Huntington Beach or no? Yeah
It's a nice fucking area. Yeah, I mean, it's okay. Let's say I'm just a huge huge city to like yours. Yeah
It's not like people think it's like I'm in LA County, actually
I mean when people say LA they usually mean like all the fucking LA everything like
Malibu all the way down to basically like San Diego kind of yeah
Yeah, I mean most of California is just like a lot of like
Of like nothing that's except for like the coast, you know, it's like that's all like all kinds of
cool stuff and
Everyone said that everyone like if you go to California you want to live on the on the coast
You know so everyone's over at the coast
Anywhere else it's so fucking expensive me most 99% of people can't afford it
Right this little show in Torrance where I was born they showed like a million dollar household for a million dollars. It was like this gutted
burnt out like
House but it's like, you know, they're probably just gonna tear it on the house
Just minimal or something up there. I don't know, but it's like
The housing market is crazy like for a million dollars. You can get like a dump
Yeah, like it's crazy, it's crazy you want to buy if you want to buy something like near the coast
Yeah, like a million dollars. You could shoot a fucking studio apartment. Yeah
Okay, dude go on inside
It's wet.
OK, well, I don't want you to do it.
You want to see the gym, psych?
Yeah, can you feel like a little working out for us
to get us motivated?
See the gym.
And then maybe with Flex.
Oh, nice.
He's got his own bench.
Nice.
Damn, dude.
And he's got like a bike, a cyclist bike, whatever.
Whatever they're called.
That's your shit.
Damn, dude.
And he's got a nice flooring.
It's got a nice set up there
Okay start working out for me. Oh, yeah, what is that? I could say we're like, hey Brandon. What's up, Brandon? How are you?
21 and a half
20 200 pounds and a half left the RV
21 and a it's neat. I love his feet. I think I'm a foot fetish
Seven and a half that is that? Oh, yeah, that's all I thought that's all your wieners
Oh, I'm sorry you're talking about something else. I'm so sorry. We're not good enough. Whatever you want. See if we didn't have good enough
I heard that women like a 666, is that true?
They like 666?
What's women like?
Just average.
They don't want a gigantic fucking elephant dick in there, ripping them apart.
They want a guy with six inches, six figures, and six foot tall.
666.
Exactly.
They still don't want to say that.
Okay. Well, I say, okay, but I think, well, actually there's women that have a small penis fetish. I mean, they're, they're great.
There are them too.
There's a few of them.
Well, the majority, the majority I've heard say that they want a 666.
The majority want the majority.
They want 10-12, they want 12 inches.
They want a 6 plus inches.
Okay, so if a woman has an elephant vagina, then she wants an elephant dick.
If a woman has that Arby's roast beef vagina.
Like a French baguette or something like that. I don't know.
If a woman has a, in Tantra, they say there's like an elephant vagina, a horse vagina, and a deer vagina.
It's really tight.
And a rabbit vagina.
Rabbit, yeah, or like something. Yeah, this is a Playboy buddy.
And you know, they also, they tunnel them to the Playboy mansion, you know that?
We'll have to see the bathroom.
Yeah, the bathroom.
Let's not finish it.
That's the nicest bathroom I've ever bathroomed. Oh shit. It is nice
Nice
What is this your man saying Joker like what are you Bruce Wayne?
Yeah, Bruce Wayne. I stopped being the Joker and I came back
This is a good that's good ass. It's actually good. I'm elegant. Join it. Try the good side Joker
Don't be a Joker be a Batman. I'm from
The upper echelon
You're from the upper echelon, so what are you like a third degree Mason? Yes
Okay
Well, I call that a porch Mason, but okay good for you. Okay. How my hand is in the light
Yeah, the hidden hand
Yeah, for us wearing the triangle. I was wearing a fucking shirt today that said a California
No, no, this is so close
Or this whatever the fuck
Yeah
California bear with the triangle fucking eyeball on it
Join her because any group that would have me I wouldn't want to join. I'm just kidding. No, I'm I'm a war log now
Okay, good. But what are you doing? Are you gonna go to Hogwarts or something?
He does look like a like a
What's about it? What crystal veil? No, Mr. LeBail. Mr. LeBail. Um, is that like a Harry Potter character?
No, Mr. LeBail is the devil. Oh, okay. I thought you were talking about Mr. Belding from Scythe Save by the Bell.
Do you know him?
No, I do. I know him. Mr. LaBelle. Let me see. Mr. LaBelle
To be to be one of the well to be part of the elites you have to be from one of the eight families
Oh, I'm from I'm from the 13th family. I'm from the 13th family called the Merovingians
From the third circle triangle of Satan and hell. Okay. That's the Dante's third circle. That's where yeah, yeah
Yeah, that one. There's one third circle. Dante's inferno
You got to be a part some of the families and they all worship mr. LeBail
Ball or bail right the bail. Yeah, the bail like but that's like Jezebel or
of the
He's cool. He's he's a friend of mine. So anyways
Be a part of the family to know mr. LeBal and if you work for mr. LeBal they they run the world
Okay, I guess I don't what it's hell. Yeah, that's how I ended up in a mansion
Well, I thought you sold your soul to the devil for money
That's not a very good. I don't think you can though except. Oh my god
I've never seen the last one. I don't believe in souls. So fuck it, dude. Whatever you gotta do to make money
That's that's stupid. No, it's not
you're an isle of the thing is that money will make your life so much easier if we do not sacrifice
always there's there's there's there's being poor sucks dude just working on that's because
you're as a dude american you have its perspective it's like there's four there's poor fishermen
in like on an island that have a little fishing boat well yeah they're on a fucking island in
tropical beautiful tropical islands in california so how about how about good i
California has all I mean there are a lot of beautiful places, but there are a lot of fucking
Shit holes too. I live in a beautiful place. And so how do you do that with money, right?
exactly
Well, I do that through
Circumstance
Circum what I'd say circumsense like
Circum do you suck them things are how things are
What what
What what would you circumcise? Yeah, I've been circumcised. Yeah, um, I didn't have a mule though at a winesteam
All right, so I gotta go plug my phone up on the charger. Okay, dude
I'll see you in a second. Okay, dude. Yeah, this whole like notion that
Making a lot of money is evil. I mean
I'm all for taxing the wealth and all for taxing billionaires
Yeah, money money is not inherently evil it's just no but money's like also just okay
It's an energy. So it's not necessarily just a material thing, right?
It's giving me an energy right and it can like lead to like, you know, it's different things and different
opportunities and things like that but
at the same time it's like the money doesn't make anybody happy it's like actually like
it's like we are but it makes it doesn't make people happy it just makes their life a lot easier
it can it can it can make them harder if you can't afford like healthcare and your fucking
dying of cancer yeah it'll definitely help you Canada that's free over there well yeah America
it's not free because we have a fucking we have billionaires and trillionaires who aren't getting
right and people other people who are poor
Getting getting poor and poor and they're starving and they can't
Fucking health care and they can't afford gas
No, I care dude, it's bullshit. That's fucked up
We live in the richest fucking country
And people are starving and can't afford health care like what the fuck is that one of the most wealthy parts in the country
So how are you like living?
I'm living fine, but I'm I care about people who aren't doing as fine as me
Being outspoken I'm saying fuck these fucking billionaires
We need a fucking tax these billionaires. That's what I'm saying
Bullshit dude
Taxes motherfucking cunts like a
Evil pieces of shit like Donald Trump making they're just looting the fucking
Treasury Department
No, every party no every party doesn't do it as well as Trump's doing it come on dude
Did Biden loot the fucking treasury as bad as Trump is?
Hell no
corrupt mother fucker in the White House in our lifetime
I don't know.
Bond is not even any, there's no comparison, dude.
I hardly even care about Trump, it's like he's an actor, he's just, he's like a...
He's an actor, he's that kid who's fucking robbing people blind, and people don't even
realize it.
Oh wait, I mean it's like, you know, he's doing that.
He's taking me off, dude.
But at the end of the day, I'm like, you know what, fuck it.
Americans voted for this guy, they voted to get Rob blinded, so whatever, let him get
Rob fucking blind.
No, my problem at the end of the day. Fuck these guys fuck fuck Trump and fuck everyone who voted for trouble
Hope you get ripped in the ass
Yes, I'm very liberal
Not very very liberal, but I'm liberal
Definitely not into Trump at all. I've never liked that fucking cocksucker. I don't know how anybody I
Don't know how anybody ever believed his bullshit from day one
Yeah, exactly there are people Americans love their actors. They love Donald Trump and
Ronald Reagan and all Schwarzenegger. Oh, he was in movies. He's I love him
You know his name is idiots. Oh, you know what Schwarzenegger means?
No, I don't know so Schwartz and there are the words Schwartz
Uh, I know it's German or Polish or something, but I don't know what it means
You just work out spartza. It's spartz
Schwarz yeah, schwarz is like black. So schwarz. Okay. So it's a black. Yeah. Yeah means black, too
Schwarz in nigga. Wow. Yeah, I never thought of that schwarz in nigga. Wow
That's kind of crazy what I know Donald Trump is
His grandfather, whoever, his great-grandfather was Trump.
It was Trump, and they changed this to Trump, because.
Here in the book, there's just a Baron von Trump,
and it's like, it's like a book written like 100 years ago,
and it has like the same exact name as like his son,
and like, it's like, there's all these six,
there was like a, it's at the park avenue,
like where Trump Tower is.
It takes place, it's like so crazy.
Yeah, I don't know, I don't know if it was one of those men.
Yeah, I mean, dude, I'm getting more, every day I'm getting more and more convinced that we're living in, uh,
we're living in the fucking, uh, what do you call it, simulation matrix, like
Donald Trump, Donald Trump, Trump, whatever, Trump, that guy probably is the, the fucking antichrist and we're all gonna,
if Jesus ever was to, uh, reave here, it's probably gonna happen in our lifetime.
Jesus um, well, yeah, but it's like maybe Jesus maybe Jesus was more like an idea like I've uh,
like for everybody to
I'm I'm with you on that. I'm actually with you on that. I don't I'm not religious, but I do believe that
the idea
of Jesus and all these like
These martyrs and stuff is good for me humanity because it keeps people in check tip tells people like what?
Had to live your life
Not enough people are fucking I guess I'm one of them because I don't really follow religion, but none of people are
Ah and a lot of these motherfuckers who voted for Trump are super religious and they're like
They voted for the fucking anti-Christ god damn it
Yeah
Fucking Zionist extremists, I mean, I don't know about like the word
There's not it's not just Jewish is
Zionists, it's Christians, Zionists too.
Right, but they're very, I mean it's-
They're fucking psychotic, dude.
They actually want to bring,
they actually want ushering like the end of the world
and bring back Jesus.
Yeah, I mean, but that's like,
and then that's like, that's like a terrorist.
It's like a, you know, it's like the most-
Dude, exactly, that's what I'm saying.
And people don't-
There's there's more
American terrorists than there are Iranian terrorists or
Indian terrorists, right? But that's when you when you say that they're like, oh you you hate America
I hate fucking terrorists, right?
But it's like yeah, it's like there are domestic terrorists, but it's like I think that was kind of like one of the things
They tried to get like oh, you know bin Laden everything and they said they said oh take away all the privacy laws
I take away like the
They took 9-11 away. Oh, oh
We we let 9-11 happen. So we're so vulnerable. We need a mass surveillance. We need the Patriot Act to keep us as safe
Right. I mean, it's like, you know
Because all we have is the law, really, and what is law? It's just a made-up thing, right?
Law, yeah. Law is just rules that keep people in check. That's all it is.
That's what everything is, you know. Basically, it's like, you know, that's what I mean.
I mean, there are good laws, but I mean, fuck, dude.
Well, how many of the ten commandments are actual laws?
None of them.
Take Donald Trump, and he embodies every...
Every negative like he embodies all seven sins to the fucking core
No, it's like I think that's like a Scandinavian
It's like a it's like Scandinavian heaven Valhalla when you die you go to Valhalla
Yeah, and the Valkyrie chose to choose to fall on soldiers like you have to die brave and like a war or something like that
So they want to die like that. They want to
Some psychotic we got a kill we got a kill the the other fucking
Tribal tribe in
Right, it's like oh, it's basically the same kind of people like
These dumb for sports fans that they're like, you know
Oh, yeah, sports analysis is definitely a tribalism, but it's not killing people. It's just beating them at a sport
Well, I mean, that's like that's like learning team dynamics and it's learning cooperation. It's also like learning
Yeah
Teamwork all that leadership
Because you learn like to look at like people's strengths because it's like it doesn't matter what race or anything
It's like you have to like yeah, that's why I love sports because it's not about
It's not about race. It's not about everybody. Just if you're if you're good if you're a leader and you're good at like teamwork and
Companionship and you're good at let's get this fucking job done. That's that's what it's all about
I don't give a shit if you're black white Jewish gay, whatever
What job do you want to get that one?
I want peace and harmony on the world peace and harmony
Peace implies peace implies war because in order to like protect it does kind of yeah, you're right
But it implies it nice if there was a world without war and everybody was
But would you get would you be thriving and there weren't billionaires?
Fucking leaching and sucking the blood of the poor people
But you really think, I mean, you really think that's the biggest problem, I think it's just billionaires.
I do, I do. I think billionaires, trillionaires are one of the biggest problems in the industry.
There's like a hundred of them in the world. I mean, there's not that many of them, right?
It's like a very rare kind of like, I think a billion dollars, right?
There's not very many of them.
Well, it's not that many of them, but there's a lot of people living paycheck to paycheck and that's a problem
There's not many who are gonna die and distribute their wealth
It's like Warren Buffett said he's gonna donate his money. That's a good thing
A lot of these motherfuckers are not gonna donate their money. They're gonna
They're not gonna they're not gonna they're not gonna Donald Trump is gonna if oh when I die
I'm gonna donate my money to Africa and starving kids
Because there's other opportunities and things that that they come along with it being Donald Trump's child, right?
It's so I mean it's like no get hired rubber, you know, I mean it's like
Right, it means like their celebrities basically
Don't need these motherfuckers. We don't need billionaires. Sorry, dude
We can make the world work without billionaires
Oh, I need I need billions and billions of dollars so we can go to Mars and build a colony there
We're only rich people go on
We'll target we'll target the world and blow them up and take their fucking resources and build shit on Mars and
Fuck that
Well, I mean, they're not even going to Mars, they just go to Arizona.
They are going to, dude, you don't think you, what?
Mars is not real. Mars is not real. We're going to Mars.
Mars isn't real?
No. None of the planets are real.
Oh, uh, what?
Have you ever looked at them close up? They don't look anything like they're depicted.
They're always just these, these, these arcs.
So the sun isn't real, or the moon isn't real, or the sun might be, but what is it?
Like, what is it really? It's like, it's like, uh,
It's a giant ball of burning hydrogen and giant ball floating in the sky. Yeah
The giant ball of elements that this just been burning for billions of years because it's so fucking huge
It's a camera now
Now I believe the planets are real believe Mars is real believe you on and is
Fucked hard billionaires want to go there and oh
We'll be safe if we build a little calling on Mars. They can't bomb affair
No one's going to Mars, but do you ever see South Park where they go if they're not going to Mars
They're going underground right you at least believe that they're going into the fuck
They don't want to live there, but they will they definitely will if they
They have well, yeah
Do you have a pass do you have a pass to uh if there's a like a
Clear fallout will they let you underground to go? Oh, I'm
It's if you have to have like the uh, you have to buy it ahead of time and stuff and of course
It's a rich club and you're not invited. Well, who cares it? You know, I care, dude
But you want to be in there with them?
No, I want to fucking kill him dude. That's what I want to do. I want to kill his motherfuckers
You're just talking so extreme that it's like it's hard to take me seriously because it's like
How's that extreme that I want to kill billionaires and stuff like that you want to kill billionaires because you're thinking they're doing
Yeah, I want to kill I want to kill the people who are I want to kill the people who are running the world
Yeah, because the world is fucked up. Well, but you should really say that because they're running the world
So they're I don't give a shit dude. They can come and arrest me. I don't care
No, they can do more than a recipe, but it's like I don't
Like just just talk about what the talk guys about the world's child's please. Let's talk about a bologna and cheese sandwiches
Yeah, vlog now, I want to be bologna in you so I know you do I want to be bologna in
Samo-hi, I can penelope cruise
All right, let's go to me and you. Let's go to Castro district and we'll
We'll find some good guys and some hot chicks and have an orgy
Okay, so it's fun. Yeah
I'm on your team and in the sake that like all
I will do whatever I can to like talk up. It's like, oh, this guy, this guy's shaky. He's my, he's my best friend, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's
Well, it's so fucking late. Yeah, so if you've you've you've seen this this gigantic sea lion in
San Francisco Harbor
Oh, yeah, Monterey has like a gigantic aquarium and the San Francisco Museum of Science is fucking dope too. Yeah
I mean, I'm just so fucking dope. Have you ever been there before? Yeah, I just live in I lived in
Menlo, and so I'd like
Francisco for like the weekends and like for like it's called Maritime Hall. I don't know if you've heard of that
Yeah, it's like it's like four is like it's like I saw like suicidal tendencies. That's a war
It's tight
Said gore Wow
I see people know gore or even mention gore. That's how you mentioned gore. Yeah
That's another thing it's cool about San Francisco is they have just crazy ass bands like that who are super
Yeah
Rave in the next room and then there'd be a gossip in the third room. Yeah, exactly
Oh, it's like it's like there's three like every like little like thing and then it's yeah
Like it was just fun and like that and people are like doing drugs and like oh, you're liquid assets. Yeah, seriously
It's like San Francisco is like a Disneyland for our adults. Yeah to me
You heard of this. We were heard of a band called oxbow. Oh
XMO
O X B O W oxbow
Yeah, the singer they're from San Francisco the singer is like this fucking big-ass buff black dude who will beat anybody's ass
But at the same time he wears like bra and panties on stage
Might be a man you're into oxbow and fucking tight oxbow like them a lot
There were one of the albums has um, what's the black guy from the rat pack?
Oh, it's Sammy Davis Jr.
Sammy Davis, yeah.
One of their albums has Sammy Davis Jr. on the cover
and it's like, I think the album's called
The King of All Jews.
Yeah.
Sammy Davis Jr.
Yeah, Oxbow, how fuck with them, heavy, they're tight.
Yeah, well, the king of the Jews was Jesus.
The king of the Jews, yeah.
But it's the king of the Jews
and then it shows a picture of Sammy Davis Jr.
Yeah, well, because he was like in this recently Jewish one.
The Rat Pack was that much of Jewish stuff at Sammy Davis Junior.
Was it all Jews?
I mean, I know there were Sammy Davis juniors, Frank Sinatra, were they?
They were all fucking Jews.
I think they had all the bases covered in Jewish.
That's tight. They had all the bases, the Blacks, the G's, the Italians, the Harvey Oswald. Yeah, he was a transgender. He was a transvestite and had a boyfriend and stuff like that.
He was probably one of the people who was on the Kennedy assassination.
Yeah, I mean, I don't doubt it. There's some fucking weird ass shit going on behind the scenes with the CIA and everything.
Yeah.
I don't doubt it at all.
Can't talk too much about it because a lot of them are in my chat. So
Are they?
Welcome dude. These fucking Jews out here. I mean, I like Jews. I just don't like I just don't like Zionists
Well, I mean I don't just people by their race or they're they're
When I say Zionists, I mean
Jews Nazis white supremacists anything to do anybody who believes in ethnic cleansing get the fuck out of my fucking life
Do you know pull your fucking head off dude? Fuck you call it the kitchen?
Or could you could you tune? Yeah, it's like
It's in the cocoon or something cocoon a lot to do to cocoon Olam
and that means like the cleansing or whatever and it's like basically that
cleansing fuck fuck uh i'm not euthanasia what's it called the
it's called like the what was it called when when hillar wanted to not euthanize but oh
eugenics eugenics fuck that fuck eugenics fuck killing people like
Before we practice eugenics still do you think like people with Down syndrome should be allowed up children? Oh
That's a tough one
Is that the eugenics thing? No saying no would be eugenics because that's controlling the gene
It is eugenics to the end of the day. So I would be contradictory if I said no
So, I don't know dude. It's I mean, I'm the type to throw out those questions and that's why I like a camera
I appreciate those questions because I think of the same shit
I mean, it's interesting, but I do, I mean, I do think that they're like, you know, but they're like basically like, it needs to be taking care of their whole life, you know, I mean, if you really, I think.
Yeah, should, should people who need to be taking care of their whole life, should they be making more of themselves?
But they don't know, they see, they don't understand what they're getting into and like other people do. And so it's like, so I think that's part of it. It's like, you need to like.
Protect them from I mean the circumstance happened because that's like having a teenager like all your life
Basically because it's like a pregnant
I'll tell you this. I'd rather have I'd rather
Have a system where we can care for people who are
retarded and they
You can choose to have more children. I think the world was in a better place would be
helping them rather than
feeding
Rather than funneling more and more money to these fucking billionaires, we just want to make our lives cheerier
Yeah
Well, sometimes they do but sometimes they mean it's like the economy is interesting thing
It's like, you know, because people can get rich here doing the same things
And so it's like are you gonna begrudge people for being rich when everyone else is trying to get rich?
I mean, that's the thing like I'm for I'm for capitalism over communism, but
Think there should be a cap on how much money when when you're making
Quadrillions of the fucking dollars like this. You should be taxed out the ass
That's my feeling well
You don't need hundreds of fucking billions of dollars dude. Come on right all people are starving
Yeah, you don't I mean you don't need it, but it's like
It will be distributed in like one way or another, you know, I mean eventually it does, you know, so
But a lot of these retards the people who vote for Trump are like, no, I don't I don't want to I don't want to help poor people
I don't want poor Mexicans living. I don't want any I don't want them to have health care
I want the billionaires to get richer and richer and richer
Well, it's like that's like
People can like imagine if you'd like work for a billionaire or something that's like then you became like the massage therapist at Google
When before Google that public did people who work at Amazon? Yeah, Jeff Bezos have
Many and many of them have complained about how shitty they're fucking
How shitty their work experience is and how they're just
Basically modern-day slaves, right? Well, I mean it's like yeah, because it's very automated and it's like well
It's like in the Asian countries. They have everything like a monitor now like you were like a little thing
So if you stop working or hey, hey
Yeah, so everybody has everyone doing there's a
Karen's in the shadows of Karen. Um, so um, yeah, I don't know. So so what are we gonna meet? Are you gonna come driving pick me up tomorrow?
Set off a long drive. What about are they gonna build this? Uh, it's got them
Train station. What is it called the auto?
Autobahn
It's like a it's like a train that it's gonna be super fast
It's gonna
Okay, it's like the Liberals wanted to do it and then they got shut off
During Trump or something and then now they're going. Oh
Alright, we're actually gonna actually gonna build it this time and it's gonna cost hundreds of billions of dollars
They're gonna make a highway or a high-speed train or some shit that goes from LA to San Francisco
Yeah, you heard about that or no. Well, yeah, I've heard of that
But it's like, you know, I mean, you can take a plane too and it's like
Yeah, it's going to be a lot cheaper
If you play if you pay for the plane ticket, I'll pay for the gas and come pick you up and drive around San Francisco
Down to hangout okay
Go to the Castro will go to a
We'll go
I'm not fat at all. I'm like pretty normal. I'm like 175
None not a fat not a big fat
I'm like your age or in your 40s like all like later 30s. Yeah
Okay, I feel I'm like old physically, but I feel young at heart. So that's good
What do I look like? Uh
Brown hair blue eyes, but I have my head shaved white. Oh my god, Indian Navy and Germanic. Oh
Pretty hot, dude. No, I'm not really in it guys, but not really, but I'm looking at like masculine looking sort of
That's what I'm saying like I'll
I'll be the masculine dude. I'll be like
I'm gonna I'm gonna talking to the people who I'm gonna talking to like gay guys and just be like
Yeah, I can't really
For me but my boy my boy psych over here. It's like what kind of what what kind of guys you and do black white or what?
Mexicans there's a ton of them in the mission district
Yeah, Latinos and
Like most of them mostly like the gang memory type and so it's like everything
You're into notainos or what?
So it's the Serenios here for them. Serenios? Oh, it's notainos. If you go up to fucking mission district, you better not wear blue
Yeah, oh my gosh, but I'm gonna take you to a Dodger game
Yeah, missions like full of fucking notainos and blacks not too many
Your son annual you might want to like get some protection if you're in that area
Got a lot of them like San Jose San Francisco all that shit Oakland
Experienced life
If you can yeah, we can drive around Oakland. I'll take you through the ghetto
Find some fucking black eyes. So let's crack and cock
Wow, and uh, okay. Yeah, fuck around Santa Cruz gets it get some mushrooms
I'm not yeah, probably not. I'll help you though
If it's a woman, I will but I'm not in the guys if it's a guy in a wig. No
No, can't do it. It's me up face down. No, can't can't do it. No offense, but I can't
I'm not attracted to wieners
Trip is off
Visit Joker and I heard Atlanta's full of gay guys. Well, yeah
Joker you hear that
You know Joker and I, we spoke, Joker and I know each other from Brokebite Mountain.
We can spend some time together.
Why are you laughing?
Cause it's funny.
It is funny.
Hold on one second.
I'm gonna put it up here.
It's really funny.
Is that it's true?
Hold on one second.
He actually also, he arrested me when I was Charles Manson.
Let's see.
It's called Broke-yag Mountain actually.
I don't know why they call it Broke-yag Mountain, but...
That's not very nice. Okay. You heard that have you heard a brookie egg mountain?
Brookie egg mountain? No. Yeah, okay, but you'll rule now
Okay
Let me see if this guy's name is a trip kick. Are you a trip kick?
I think I'm a trip kick. Yeah, he's like a clipper
Yeah
So actually, I'm in a lot of his videos. I'm in like quite a bit
But I was one of the first videos that I was ever in
It was
Jokers in it. And so you get to see
Very romantic. Oh, this is it. Okay. So now I'm almost there. Let me see. Where's Joker?
Oh, here it is. I found it here. Now, you didn't believe me, but look
What do you see this? Oh shit, what I just do
What's that?
Here.
Are you a waistline?
Always has its own...
Remember the time in Brookback Mountain?
If you're looking for work, I suggest you get in here in front of...
Sikes Bussy is convulsing.
Well, since we're going to be working together,
I reckon it's time we start drinking together.
What's Bussy?
Did your asshole was, uh, perky?
Perky ladies?
Kiss the bride.
Do you know somebody named Jack?
It was fishing buddies.
Can we take my shirt off?
You know, it could be like this.
Just like this always.
This thing grabbed hold of us in the wrong place.
And we're dead.
Boy, it's your friend a way to make the 10th pass the deer.
You don't go up there to fish me.
You don't know nothing about it.
You know, 30 diamond asses to see my wear.
Are you sure?
You have no idea how bad it gets.
You can't fix it.
You gotta stand.
What the fuck?
I wish I knew you quit you.
Is that a joke?
What the fuck?
Nice shit?
Is that Joker?
That is Joker, isn't it?
Oh my god.
Joker.
What are you doing, dude?
What's so funny?
You're laughing at me?
I'm laughing at Joker because he claims to be a straight guy.
He also says he woke up happy with the guy sucking his dick in when he did?
Oh, shit. Oh low blow blow. No, but do you know he did? Did he punch him? No, he let him finish
Well, that's kind of gay
Kinda
Well, you didn't punch you. I didn't let the motherfucker finish, but I should have I should have killed them dude
If there was if it wasn't such a thing as prison, how would I fucking kill them?
Well, I don't want to go to prison for life just for beating a fucking motherfuckers face in
The U.S. Treasury's new digital payout mandate is a direct threat to the autonomy of social security recipients and
Black fucking midget beat his ass
What the fuck are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
Fucking bigger
What the fuck are you talking about?
Kind of
You know, I'm saying that that's why you didn't on there touch my shit on there
Bet you don't want nobody I bring around here. Yeah, what touch me?
Now what now what?
Exactly Chris K. Chris K. My boy. This nigga deserved
Man, I ain't right in the chair.
Come on, man, come on, man.
I just want to get you out of here.
You both are just-
You want to get your ass over there?
Get your ass over there?
I'm not playing with you.
I'm not-
Now what?
What's up?
In the suit.
ENCATERS! ENCATERS!
Fuck you, nigger! Get the fuck out of here!
ENCATERS HERE!
Get out of here! Get out of here, nigger!
Yay, so won't you collapse like a fucking lawn chair?
Get out of here! I'm white and you're not!
Shut the fuck up, Chris K.
Let me see. How about this one?
Um, the vlogger. Let me see.
Let me see. Where am I? That's what I'm looking for.
Uh, oh, hold on.
Okay, Sam Rae just unbeat this kid, that sounds good.
Um, let's see what else.
Is that Sam Rax?
Okay, here.
Um, Grace Thorpe, I don't know what that, oh, here I am, there's Tommy James, okay.
Um...
You got anything on, uh, you said, what's his name, uh...
Well blogger has ruby red fucking but a butthole ruby red butthole
But if yeah, it was it was actually show it show it can you show it back show it looks a bit
It's blowing a balloon
You see this one, this is good
If you're over 60 with money in an IRA or 401k, a federal law that just completed its rollout is the...
Everybody felt they were there at the beginning of the great experiment.
Like we were the chosen people.
The one's agenda was simply to raise the consciousness of humanity that was his goal.
America was land of promise.
It was my conviction.
We will have no problems.
We will have no problems if we all convert to things with religion.
3, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3
Oh
If the government does decide to get you they're going to get you
There is bias, there is pre-judgment, religious discrimination, and this is democracy. I've had enough of it.
We are going to amount a full-scale assault.
We will be ready to protect ourselves.
I've grown up understanding they'll shoot, not killed.
What had happened?
There's darkness in all of us.
Doesn't make you a bad person.
You know, Christine told her own son, go jump off a bridge, and then she said, he did,
but it's been to like an alligator-invested pond or something, it's a very confusing
story at all right now.
It was a very confusing story.
First of all, why would she say that to her son?
Second of all, she said it, why would she then say don't?
I mean, but she did say jump off a bridge.
It's okay.
Christine, I said sacrifice babies in the woods. You can tell me to uh jump off a bridge, okay?
But you know, then they're saying, oh, I was so drunk as a skunk. Hey, first of all,
really? Oh, I don't really drink.
Beta, beta, you don't really drink. Almost every time I hear you, you're so fucking drunk as a skunk.
I can't even barely hear your high-pitched Minnie Mouse voice.
How many wings have you built on the White Claw factory?
How many wings have they built?
How many cars do the executives of White Claw own?
Just based on your monthly consumption.
And you're telling me,
I know he's drunk!
I mean that was a little bit ridiculous and what why is it anybody saying anything to her? Oh
Not only you're a mean drunk. I mean, maybe I'm a sober
Bothering the lady at the Tempur pedic mattress store. That was a little bit low
I didn't like what he did at the fish counter either asking for a poop fish. That's really inappropriate poop fish
But then
The minute like he thinks it's his human right to come on my panel, right? He's like, oh my god. He wouldn't let me on his
You're not an interesting guest. I mean, it's like you're just like so
pompous and like oh
I mean Tommy what do you think you're you know, but you're not Tom Cruise or I don't know
Tommy Lee Jones or whatever. I don't know. Tommy James.
You're that dumb. You're Tommy James.
You're Tommy James.
You're not him. I heard you rap with Alexandra.
Shameful.
Even if that says anything about my music, you have to hear the rain falls down their duet.
Okay, I don't want to put it on her, but she's now she's posted more stuff.
She posted good times as Jewish, beat as Jewish.
Let me see, I'll say, yeah, there's same man, form bomb me, same form bomb me.
Here's Michael Jackson.
Let this mineral melt in your mouth to transform your oral health rebuilding your gums and teeth
You suck you fucking suck bitch
Yeah person sending people to my house the last
Okay, that was pretty funny, huh?
Well, there's maybe one more in YouTube, but yeah, so what are you doing today?
me uh
I don't know just some work
You're just gonna be in your basketball shorts lounging around probably most likely
Getting drunk, but now I get some like shit to do. I got like I got a feel the moe. I got um
We're tilling to do you're tilling to do roto roto tilling
Okay, you're cutting up the dirt and the ground and so you can plant shit. I got a I got a compost
Fucking cut up
Yeah, I got my plate three four. I got fucking wood to chop up with chainsaws
It sounds like a plan.
Yeah, chop up like 12 inch to 14 inch cuts of wood and then stack them up so they can
be thrown in the fireplace.
That's not very big.
Yeah.
12 inches.
I mean, that's kind of like it's not long.
I mean, but okay.
It's pretty, it's not very long.
I like it.
How about like six, eight inches of width?
Is that pretty big or no?
Eight inches of width.
Wait, how do you cut this with a saw?
Chainsaw, yeah.
Got like a feel the cut your ass. So it doesn't catch on fire and burn everything
So you got we get a lot of goddamn fires. I don't know if you know that about like California
Oh, yeah back to
Either way I'm your
Michael Jackson the verdict tackles
I keep falling in the light
I'm stretching in the voice
Permanent halo around my mind
You did not touch
Under my thumb
He's dimming down on my thoughts
They live in my blood
Seeping on my back like an offering
Watching so much I might be a rose
Say what your chest don't whisper it
I'm trying to be better but the better I try
The worse I'll pray
I will buy our slow-fade death in his promise. I never agreed to pay
It's so cool.
It's cool.
the blood on the bed she's glistening
It's so cool.
oh wow it's so hot in here
it's so hot to be a baby musician
because you have to sing like me now
talking for the burn, kiss me
promise I'll never learn
with all the ghosts I've felt
lingering in a place of dying slow
the sunlight on my bed
you say you wanna
is the only God I ever did a prayer
and he did you do
Christians from somewhere
All in kings talking in broken frequencies
Nick sings witch wolves in the static glow
with 333 where the strange things grow
while Psyche studies every face
like a predator
Great flu be seen like addicts chasing
was an issue
in a moment they thought a thing
that would
breathe and smoke through electric skin
you know ghost walking through
carrying storms nobody else could keep
Like searchlights cutting through disguise
Hearing truth underneath the silence
Breaks every masked crack
I'm all the wolves attacked in pain
Into signals signal into flame now strangers
Whisper your hidden name
You get to a dying age
Apart from laughing inside the case
They said stays
Strangers from the edge turned into another sacred pledge